[
    {
        "Front": "あいかわらず",
        "Back": "as ever,as usual,the same",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "アイデア/アイディア",
        "Back": "idea",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "あいまい",
        "Back": "vague,ambiguous",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "遭う",
        "Back": "to meet,to encounter (undesirable nuance)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 0
    },
    {
        "Front": "扇ぐ",
        "Back": "to fan,to flap",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1
    },
    {
        "Front": "青白い",
        "Back": "pale,pallid",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2
    },
    {
        "Front": "あかんぼう",
        "Back": "baby",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "明き",
        "Back": "room,time to spare,emptiness",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3
    },
    {
        "Front": "あきれる",
        "Back": "to be amazed,to be shocked",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "アクセント",
        "Back": "accent",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "あくび",
        "Back": "yawn",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "飽くまで",
        "Back": "to the end,to the last,stubbornly",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 4
    },
    {
        "Front": "明け方",
        "Back": "dawn",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 5
    },
    {
        "Front": "揚げる",
        "Back": "to lift,to fry",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 6
    },
    {
        "Front": "挙げる",
        "Back": "to raise,to fly",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 7
    },
    {
        "Front": "あげる (=やる)",
        "Back": "to do for",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "憧れる",
        "Back": "to long for,to yearn after,to admire",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 8
    },
    {
        "Front": "足跡",
        "Back": "footprints",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 9
    },
    {
        "Front": "味わう",
        "Back": "to taste,to savor,to relish",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 10
    },
    {
        "Front": "預かる",
        "Back": "to keep in custody,to receive on deposit,to take charge of",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 11
    },
    {
        "Front": "暖まる",
        "Back": "to warm up,to get warm",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 12
    },
    {
        "Front": "暖める",
        "Back": "to warm,to heat",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 13
    },
    {
        "Front": "あたりまえ",
        "Back": "usual,common,ordinary",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "あひら",
        "Back": "",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "あちらこちら",
        "Back": "here and there",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "厚かましい",
        "Back": "impudent,shameless,brazen",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 15
    },
    {
        "Front": "圧縮",
        "Back": "compression,condensation,pressure",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 16
    },
    {
        "Front": "宛名",
        "Back": "address,direction",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 17
    },
    {
        "Front": "あてはまる",
        "Back": "to be applicable,to come under (a category),to fulfill",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "あてはめる",
        "Back": "to apply,to adapt",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "暴れる",
        "Back": "to act violently,to rage,to struggle,to be riotous",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 18
    },
    {
        "Front": "脂",
        "Back": "fat,tallow,lard",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 19
    },
    {
        "Front": "あぶる",
        "Back": "to scorch",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "あふれる",
        "Back": "to flood,to overflow,to brim over",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "雨戸",
        "Back": "sliding storm door",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 20
    },
    {
        "Front": "甘やかす",
        "Back": "to pamper,to spoil",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 21
    },
    {
        "Front": "余る",
        "Back": "to remain,to be left over,to be in excess,to be too many",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 22
    },
    {
        "Front": "編物",
        "Back": "knitting,web",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 23
    },
    {
        "Front": "編む",
        "Back": "to knit",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 24
    },
    {
        "Front": "危うい",
        "Back": "dangerous,critical,grave",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 25
    },
    {
        "Front": "怪しい",
        "Back": "suspicious,dubious,doubtful",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 26
    },
    {
        "Front": "荒い",
        "Back": "rough,rude,wild",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 27
    },
    {
        "Front": "粗い",
        "Back": "coarse,rough",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 28
    },
    {
        "Front": "あらすじ",
        "Back": "outline,summary",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "争う",
        "Back": "to dispute,to argue,to be at variance,to compete",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 29
    },
    {
        "Front": "改めて",
        "Back": "another time,again,over again,anew,formally",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 30
    },
    {
        "Front": "改める",
        "Back": "to change,to alter,to reform,to revise",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 31
    },
    {
        "Front": "著す",
        "Back": "to write,to publish",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 32
    },
    {
        "Front": "有難い",
        "Back": "grateful,thankful,welcome,appreciated,evoking gratitude",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 33
    },
    {
        "Front": "在る",
        "Back": "to live,to be",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 34
    },
    {
        "Front": "あれこれ",
        "Back": "one thing or another,this and that,this or that",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "あわただしい",
        "Back": "busy,hurried,confused,flurried",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "あわてる",
        "Back": "to become confused",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "安易",
        "Back": "easy-going",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 35
    },
    {
        "Front": "案外",
        "Back": "unexpectedly",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 36
    },
    {
        "Front": "アンテナ",
        "Back": "antenna",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "言い出す",
        "Back": "to start talking,to speak,to tell,to propose,to suggest,to break the ice",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 37
    },
    {
        "Front": "言い付ける",
        "Back": "to tell,to tell on (someone),to order",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 38
    },
    {
        "Front": "意義",
        "Back": "meaning,significance",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 39
    },
    {
        "Front": "生き生き",
        "Back": "vividly,lively",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 40
    },
    {
        "Front": "いきなり",
        "Back": "(uk) abruptly,suddenly,all of a sudden,without warning",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "育児",
        "Back": "childcare,nursing,upbringing",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 41
    },
    {
        "Front": "幾分",
        "Back": "somewhat",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 42
    },
    {
        "Front": "生け花",
        "Back": "(1) flower arrangement",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 43
    },
    {
        "Front": "以後",
        "Back": "after this,from now on,hereafter,thereafter",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 44
    },
    {
        "Front": "以降",
        "Back": "on and after,hereafter,thereafter",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 45
    },
    {
        "Front": "イコール",
        "Back": "equal",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "勇ましい",
        "Back": "brave,valiant,gallant,courageous",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 46
    },
    {
        "Front": "衣食住",
        "Back": "necessities of life (food, clothing, etc.)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 47
    },
    {
        "Front": "意地悪",
        "Back": "malicious,ill-tempered,unkind",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 48
    },
    {
        "Front": "いちいち",
        "Back": "one by one,separately",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "一応",
        "Back": "once,tentatively,in outline,for the time being",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 49
    },
    {
        "Front": "一段と",
        "Back": "greater,more,further,still more",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 50
    },
    {
        "Front": "一流",
        "Back": "first class,top grade,foremost,top-notch",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 51
    },
    {
        "Front": "佚",
        "Back": "be lost,peace,hide,mistake,beautiful,in turn",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 52
    },
    {
        "Front": "一昨日",
        "Back": "day before yesterday",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 53
    },
    {
        "Front": "一昨年",
        "Back": "year before last",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 54
    },
    {
        "Front": "一斉",
        "Back": "simultaneous,all at once",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 55
    },
    {
        "Front": "一旦",
        "Back": "once,for a moment,one morning,temporarily",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 56
    },
    {
        "Front": "一定",
        "Back": "fixed,settled,definite",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 57
    },
    {
        "Front": "いっていらっしゃい",
        "Back": "",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "いってらっしゃい",
        "Back": "",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "いってまいります",
        "Back": "",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "いつのまにか",
        "Back": "before one knows,unnoticed,unawares",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "移転",
        "Back": "moving,transfer,demise",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 58
    },
    {
        "Front": "井戸",
        "Back": "water well",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 59
    },
    {
        "Front": "緯度",
        "Back": "latitude (nav.)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 60
    },
    {
        "Front": "従姉妹",
        "Back": "cousin (female)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 61
    },
    {
        "Front": "威張る",
        "Back": "to be proud,to swagger",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 62
    },
    {
        "Front": "嫌がる",
        "Back": "to hate,to dislike",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 63
    },
    {
        "Front": "いよいよ",
        "Back": "more and more,all the more,increasingly,at last,beyond doubt",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "煎る",
        "Back": "to parch,to fry",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 64
    },
    {
        "Front": "炒る",
        "Back": "",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 65
    },
    {
        "Front": "入れ物",
        "Back": "container,case,receptacle",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 66
    },
    {
        "Front": "インキ",
        "Back": "ink",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "インタビュー",
        "Back": "interview",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "引力",
        "Back": "gravity",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 67
    },
    {
        "Front": "ウーマン",
        "Back": "woman",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ウール",
        "Back": "wool",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ウエートレス",
        "Back": "waitress",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "植木",
        "Back": "garden shrubs,trees,potted plant",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 68
    },
    {
        "Front": "飢える",
        "Back": "to starve",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 69
    },
    {
        "Front": "浮ぶ",
        "Back": "to float,to rise to surface,to come to mind",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 70
    },
    {
        "Front": "浮かべる",
        "Back": "to float,to express,to look (sad, glad)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 71
    },
    {
        "Front": "浮く",
        "Back": "to float,to become merry,to become loose",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 72
    },
    {
        "Front": "承る",
        "Back": "(hum) to hear,to be told,to know",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 73
    },
    {
        "Front": "受取",
        "Back": "receipt",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 74
    },
    {
        "Front": "受け持つ",
        "Back": "to take (be in) charge of",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 75
    },
    {
        "Front": "薄暗い",
        "Back": "dim,gloomy",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 76
    },
    {
        "Front": "薄める",
        "Back": "to dilute,to water down",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 77
    },
    {
        "Front": "打合せ",
        "Back": "business meeting,previous arrangement,appointment",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 78
    },
    {
        "Front": "打ち消す",
        "Back": "to deny,to negate,to contradict",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 79
    },
    {
        "Front": "討つ",
        "Back": "to attack,to avenge",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 80
    },
    {
        "Front": "うっかり",
        "Back": "carelessly,thoughtlessly,inadvertently",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "映す",
        "Back": "to project,to reflect,to cast (shadow)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 81
    },
    {
        "Front": "写る",
        "Back": "to be photographed,to be projected",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 82
    },
    {
        "Front": "映る",
        "Back": "to be reflected,to harmonize with,to come out (photo)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 83
    },
    {
        "Front": "うどん",
        "Back": "noodles (Japanese)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "有無",
        "Back": "yes or no,existence,flag indicator (comp),presence or absence marker",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 84
    },
    {
        "Front": "埋める",
        "Back": "to bury,to fill up,to fill (a seat, a vacant position)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 85
    },
    {
        "Front": "敬う",
        "Back": "to show respect,to honour",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 86
    },
    {
        "Front": "裏返す",
        "Back": "to turn inside out,to turn (something) over",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 87
    },
    {
        "Front": "裏口",
        "Back": "backdoor,rear entrance",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 88
    },
    {
        "Front": "占う",
        "Back": "to forecast,to predict",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 89
    },
    {
        "Front": "恨み",
        "Back": "resentment",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 90
    },
    {
        "Front": "恨む",
        "Back": "to curse,to feel bitter",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 91
    },
    {
        "Front": "羨ましい",
        "Back": "envious,enviable",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 92
    },
    {
        "Front": "羨む",
        "Back": "to envy",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 93
    },
    {
        "Front": "売上",
        "Back": "amount sold,proceeds",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 94
    },
    {
        "Front": "売り切れ",
        "Back": "sold-out",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 95
    },
    {
        "Front": "売り切れる",
        "Back": "to be sold out",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 96
    },
    {
        "Front": "売行き",
        "Back": "sales",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 97
    },
    {
        "Front": "うろうろ",
        "Back": "loiteringly,aimless wandering",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "運河",
        "Back": "canal,waterway",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 98
    },
    {
        "Front": "うんと",
        "Back": "a great deal,very much",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "英文",
        "Back": "sentence in English",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 99
    },
    {
        "Front": "英和",
        "Back": "English-Japanese (e.g. dictionary)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 100
    },
    {
        "Front": "ええと",
        "Back": "let me see,well,er....",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "液体",
        "Back": "liquid,fluid",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 101
    },
    {
        "Front": "エチケット",
        "Back": "etiquette",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "絵の具",
        "Back": "colors,paints",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 102
    },
    {
        "Front": "エプロン",
        "Back": "apron",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "偉い",
        "Back": "great,celebrated,eminent,terrible,awful,famous,remarkable,excellent",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 103
    },
    {
        "Front": "宴会",
        "Back": "party,banquet",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 104
    },
    {
        "Front": "園芸",
        "Back": "horticulture,gardening",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 105
    },
    {
        "Front": "演劇",
        "Back": "play (theatrical)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 106
    },
    {
        "Front": "円周",
        "Back": "circumference",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 107
    },
    {
        "Front": "遠足",
        "Back": "trip,hike,picnic",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 108
    },
    {
        "Front": "延長",
        "Back": "extension,elongation,prolongation,lengthening",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 109
    },
    {
        "Front": "煙突",
        "Back": "chimney",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 110
    },
    {
        "Front": "追い掛ける",
        "Back": "to chase or run after someone,to run down,to pursue",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 111
    },
    {
        "Front": "追い越す",
        "Back": "to pass (e.g. car),to outdistance,to outstrip",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 112
    },
    {
        "Front": "オイル",
        "Back": "oil,engine oil,kerosene",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "応援",
        "Back": "aid,assistance,help,reinforcement",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 113
    },
    {
        "Front": "王女",
        "Back": "princess",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 114
    },
    {
        "Front": "応ずる",
        "Back": "to answer,to respond,to meet,to satisfy,to accept",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 115
    },
    {
        "Front": "応接",
        "Back": "reception",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 116
    },
    {
        "Front": "応対",
        "Back": "receiving,dealing with",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 117
    },
    {
        "Front": "往復",
        "Back": "(col) round trip,coming and going,return ticket",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 118
    },
    {
        "Front": "欧米",
        "Back": "Europe and America,the West",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 119
    },
    {
        "Front": "応用",
        "Back": "application,put to practical use",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 120
    },
    {
        "Front": "オーケストラ",
        "Back": "orchestra",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "おおざっぱ",
        "Back": "rough (not precise),broad,sketchy",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "大通り",
        "Back": "main street",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 121
    },
    {
        "Front": "オートメーション",
        "Back": "automation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "オーバーコート",
        "Back": "",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "大凡",
        "Back": "about,roughly,as a rule,approximately",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 122
    },
    {
        "Front": "お帰り",
        "Back": "return,welcome",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 123
    },
    {
        "Front": "おかけください",
        "Back": "",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "おかげさまで",
        "Back": "Thanks to god,thanks to you",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "おかず",
        "Back": "side dish,accompaniment for rice dishes",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "拝む",
        "Back": "to worship,to beg,to make a supplication",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 124
    },
    {
        "Front": "お代わり",
        "Back": "second helping,another cup",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 125
    },
    {
        "Front": "補う",
        "Back": "to compensate for",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 126
    },
    {
        "Front": "おきのどくに",
        "Back": "",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "屋外",
        "Back": "outdoors",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 127
    },
    {
        "Front": "おくさん",
        "Back": "(hon) wife,your wife,madam",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "送り仮名",
        "Back": "part of word written in kana",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 128
    },
    {
        "Front": "おげんきで",
        "Back": "",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "怠る",
        "Back": "to neglect,to be off guard,to be feeling better",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 129
    },
    {
        "Front": "押える",
        "Back": "to stop,to restrain,to seize,to repress,to suppress,to press down",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 130
    },
    {
        "Front": "おさきに",
        "Back": "before,ahead,previously",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "納める",
        "Back": "to obtain,to reap,to pay,to supply,to accept",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 131
    },
    {
        "Front": "治める",
        "Back": "(1) to govern,to manage,(2) to subdue",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 132
    },
    {
        "Front": "惜しい",
        "Back": "regrettable,disappointing,precious",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 133
    },
    {
        "Front": "御辞儀",
        "Back": "bow",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 134
    },
    {
        "Front": "伯父さん",
        "Back": "middle-aged gentleman,uncle",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 135
    },
    {
        "Front": "小父さん",
        "Back": "middle-aged gentleman,uncle",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 136
    },
    {
        "Front": "叔父さん",
        "Back": "middle-aged gentleman,uncle",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 137
    },
    {
        "Front": "おしゃれ",
        "Back": "smartly dressed,someone smartly dressed,fashion-conscious",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "おじゃまします",
        "Back": "Excuse me for disturbing you",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "教わる",
        "Back": "to be taught",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 138
    },
    {
        "Front": "おだいじに",
        "Back": "Take care of yourself",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "落着く",
        "Back": "to calm down,to settle down",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 139
    },
    {
        "Front": "御手洗",
        "Back": "font of purifying water placed at entrance of shrine",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 140
    },
    {
        "Front": "お出掛け",
        "Back": "",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 141
    },
    {
        "Front": "お手伝いさん",
        "Back": "maid",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 142
    },
    {
        "Front": "おどかす",
        "Back": "to threaten,to coerce",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "落し物",
        "Back": "lost property",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 143
    },
    {
        "Front": "おととい",
        "Back": "day before yesterday",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "おととし",
        "Back": "year before last",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "おとなしい",
        "Back": "obedient,docile,quiet",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "驚かす",
        "Back": "to surprise,to frighten,to create a stir",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 144
    },
    {
        "Front": "おねがいします",
        "Back": "please",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "各々",
        "Back": "each,every,either,respectively,severally",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 145
    },
    {
        "Front": "伯母さん",
        "Back": "(hon) aunt",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 146
    },
    {
        "Front": "叔母さん",
        "Back": "(1) aunt,(2) middle-aged lady",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 147
    },
    {
        "Front": "おはよう",
        "Back": "(abbr) Good morning",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "お参り",
        "Back": "worship,shrine visit",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 148
    },
    {
        "Front": "おまたせしました",
        "Back": "Sorry to have kept you waiting",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "おまちください",
        "Back": "Please wait a moment",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "おまちどおさま",
        "Back": "Sorry to have kept you waiting",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "おめでたい",
        "Back": "happy event,matter for congratulation,auspicious event,pregnancy",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "思い掛けない",
        "Back": "unexpected,casual",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 149
    },
    {
        "Front": "思い込む",
        "Back": "to be under impression that,to be convinced that",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 150
    },
    {
        "Front": "思いっ切り",
        "Back": "",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 151
    },
    {
        "Front": "思い付く",
        "Back": "to think of,to hit upon",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 152
    },
    {
        "Front": "重たい",
        "Back": "heavy,massive,serious",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 153
    },
    {
        "Front": "おやすみ",
        "Back": "(1) holiday,absence,rest,(2) (exp) Good night",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "おやつ",
        "Back": "(1) between meal snack,afternoon refreshment",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "親指",
        "Back": "thumb",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 154
    },
    {
        "Front": "オルガン",
        "Back": "organ",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "卸す",
        "Back": "to sell wholesale,grated (vegetables)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 155
    },
    {
        "Front": "恩恵",
        "Back": "grace,favor,blessing,benefit",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 156
    },
    {
        "Front": "温室",
        "Back": "greenhouse",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 157
    },
    {
        "Front": "温泉",
        "Back": "spa,hot spring,onsen",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 158
    },
    {
        "Front": "温帯",
        "Back": "temperate zone",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 159
    },
    {
        "Front": "御中",
        "Back": "and Company,Messrs.",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 160
    },
    {
        "Front": "女の人",
        "Back": "woman",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 161
    },
    {
        "Front": "蚊",
        "Back": "mosquito",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 162
    },
    {
        "Front": "カーブ",
        "Back": "(1) curve,(2) curve ball (baseball)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "貝",
        "Back": "shell,shellfish",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 163
    },
    {
        "Front": "開会",
        "Back": "opening of a meeting",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 164
    },
    {
        "Front": "会館",
        "Back": "meeting hall,assembly hall",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 165
    },
    {
        "Front": "改札",
        "Back": "examination of tickets",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 166
    },
    {
        "Front": "解散",
        "Back": "breakup,dissolution",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 167
    },
    {
        "Front": "海水浴",
        "Back": "sea bathing,seawater bath",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 168
    },
    {
        "Front": "回数",
        "Back": "number of times,frequency",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 169
    },
    {
        "Front": "回数券",
        "Back": "book of tickets",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 170
    },
    {
        "Front": "改正",
        "Back": "revision,amendment,alteration",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 171
    },
    {
        "Front": "快晴",
        "Back": "good weather",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 172
    },
    {
        "Front": "解説",
        "Back": "explanation,commentary",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 173
    },
    {
        "Front": "改造",
        "Back": "(1) remodeling,(2) modding (comp)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 174
    },
    {
        "Front": "開通",
        "Back": "opening,open",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 175
    },
    {
        "Front": "回転",
        "Back": "rotation,revolution,turning",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 176
    },
    {
        "Front": "解答",
        "Back": "answer,solution",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 177
    },
    {
        "Front": "回答",
        "Back": "reply,answer",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 178
    },
    {
        "Front": "外部",
        "Back": "the outside,external",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 179
    },
    {
        "Front": "解放",
        "Back": "release,liberation,emancipation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 180
    },
    {
        "Front": "開放",
        "Back": "open,throw open,liberalization",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 181
    },
    {
        "Front": "海洋",
        "Back": "ocean",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 182
    },
    {
        "Front": "概論",
        "Back": "intro,outline,general remarks",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 183
    },
    {
        "Front": "帰す",
        "Back": "to send back",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 184
    },
    {
        "Front": "却って",
        "Back": "on the contrary,rather,all the more,instead",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 185
    },
    {
        "Front": "代える",
        "Back": "to exchange,to interchange,to substitute,to replace",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 186
    },
    {
        "Front": "反る",
        "Back": "to warp,to be warped,to curve",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 187
    },
    {
        "Front": "家屋",
        "Back": "house,building",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 188
    },
    {
        "Front": "係わる",
        "Back": "to concern oneself in,to have to do with,to affect,to influence,to stick to (opinions)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 189
    },
    {
        "Front": "書留",
        "Back": "writing down,putting on record,recording,making a note of,registration (of mail)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 190
    },
    {
        "Front": "書取",
        "Back": "dictation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 191
    },
    {
        "Front": "垣根",
        "Back": "hedge",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 192
    },
    {
        "Front": "掻く",
        "Back": "to scratch,to perspire",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 193
    },
    {
        "Front": "嗅ぐ",
        "Back": "to sniff,to smell",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 194
    },
    {
        "Front": "架空",
        "Back": "aerial,overhead,fiction,fanciful",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 195
    },
    {
        "Front": "各自",
        "Back": "individual,each",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 196
    },
    {
        "Front": "拡充",
        "Back": "expansion",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 197
    },
    {
        "Front": "学術",
        "Back": "science,learning,scholarship",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 198
    },
    {
        "Front": "各地",
        "Back": "every place,various places",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 199
    },
    {
        "Front": "拡張",
        "Back": "expansion,extension,enlargement,escape (ESC)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 200
    },
    {
        "Front": "角度",
        "Back": "angle",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 201
    },
    {
        "Front": "学年",
        "Back": "year in school,grade in school",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 202
    },
    {
        "Front": "学部",
        "Back": "department of a university,undergraduate",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 203
    },
    {
        "Front": "格別",
        "Back": "exceptional",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 204
    },
    {
        "Front": "確率",
        "Back": "probability",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 205
    },
    {
        "Front": "学力",
        "Back": "scholarship,knowledge,literary ability",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 206
    },
    {
        "Front": "掛け算",
        "Back": "multiplication",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 207
    },
    {
        "Front": "可決",
        "Back": "approval,adoption (e.g. motion, bill),passage",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 208
    },
    {
        "Front": "火口",
        "Back": "a burner,origin of a fire",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 209
    },
    {
        "Front": "下降",
        "Back": "downward,descent,fall,drop,subsidence",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 210
    },
    {
        "Front": "重なる",
        "Back": "to be piled up,lie on top of one another,overlap each other",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 211
    },
    {
        "Front": "重ねる",
        "Back": "to pile up,to put something on another,to heap up,to add,to repeat",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 212
    },
    {
        "Front": "飾り",
        "Back": "decoration",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 213
    },
    {
        "Front": "火山",
        "Back": "volcano",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 214
    },
    {
        "Front": "かしこまりました",
        "Back": "certainly!",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "貸し出し",
        "Back": "lending,loaning",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 215
    },
    {
        "Front": "過失",
        "Back": "error,blunder,accident",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 216
    },
    {
        "Front": "果実",
        "Back": "fruit,nut,berry.",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 217
    },
    {
        "Front": "貸間",
        "Back": "room to let",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 218
    },
    {
        "Front": "貸家",
        "Back": "house for rent",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 219
    },
    {
        "Front": "個所",
        "Back": "passage,place,point,part",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 220
    },
    {
        "Front": "過剰",
        "Back": "excess,over-",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 221
    },
    {
        "Front": "かじる",
        "Back": "to chew,to bite (at),to gnaw,to nibble",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "課税",
        "Back": "taxation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 222
    },
    {
        "Front": "下線",
        "Back": "underline,underscore",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 223
    },
    {
        "Front": "カセット",
        "Back": "cassette (tape)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "加速",
        "Back": "acceleration",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 224
    },
    {
        "Front": "加速度",
        "Back": "acceleration",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 225
    },
    {
        "Front": "固い",
        "Back": "stubborn,firm (not viscous or easily moved)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 226
    },
    {
        "Front": "堅い",
        "Back": "hard (esp. wood),steadfast,honorable,stuffy writing",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 227
    },
    {
        "Front": "片仮名",
        "Back": "katakana",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 228
    },
    {
        "Front": "片付く",
        "Back": "to put in order,to dispose of,to solve",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 229
    },
    {
        "Front": "塊",
        "Back": "lump,mass,clod,cluster",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 230
    },
    {
        "Front": "固まる",
        "Back": "to harden,to solidify,to become firm,to become certain",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 231
    },
    {
        "Front": "片道",
        "Back": "one-way (trip)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 232
    },
    {
        "Front": "傾く",
        "Back": "to incline toward,to slant,to lurch",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 233
    },
    {
        "Front": "片寄る",
        "Back": "to be one-sided,to incline,to be partial",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 234
    },
    {
        "Front": "学科",
        "Back": "study subject,course of study",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 235
    },
    {
        "Front": "学会",
        "Back": "scientific society,academic meeting",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 236
    },
    {
        "Front": "楽器",
        "Back": "musical instrument",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 237
    },
    {
        "Front": "学級",
        "Back": "grade in school",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 238
    },
    {
        "Front": "担ぐ",
        "Back": "to shoulder,to carry on shoulder",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 239
    },
    {
        "Front": "括弧",
        "Back": "parenthesis,brackets",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 240
    },
    {
        "Front": "活字",
        "Back": "printing type",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 241
    },
    {
        "Front": "活躍",
        "Back": "activity",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 242
    },
    {
        "Front": "活力",
        "Back": "vitality,energy",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 243
    },
    {
        "Front": "仮定",
        "Back": "assumption,supposition,hypothesis",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 244
    },
    {
        "Front": "過程",
        "Back": "process",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 245
    },
    {
        "Front": "課程",
        "Back": "course,curriculum",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 246
    },
    {
        "Front": "仮名",
        "Back": "(n) alias,pseudonym,pen name",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 247
    },
    {
        "Front": "仮名遣い",
        "Back": "kana orthography,syllabary spelling",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 248
    },
    {
        "Front": "鐘",
        "Back": "bell,chime",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 249
    },
    {
        "Front": "加熱",
        "Back": "heating",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 250
    },
    {
        "Front": "兼ねる",
        "Back": "to hold (position),to serve,to be unable",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 251
    },
    {
        "Front": "カバー",
        "Back": "cover (ex. book)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "過半数",
        "Back": "majority",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 252
    },
    {
        "Front": "被せる",
        "Back": "to cover (with something)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 253
    },
    {
        "Front": "釜",
        "Back": "iron pot,kettle",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 254
    },
    {
        "Front": "紙屑",
        "Back": "wastepaper",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 255
    },
    {
        "Front": "神様",
        "Back": "god",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 256
    },
    {
        "Front": "剃刀",
        "Back": "razor",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 257
    },
    {
        "Front": "ガム",
        "Back": "chewing gum",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "貨物",
        "Back": "cargo,freight",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 258
    },
    {
        "Front": "かゆい",
        "Back": "itchy,itching",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "歌謡",
        "Back": "song,ballad",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 259
    },
    {
        "Front": "殻",
        "Back": "shell,husk,hull,chaff",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 260
    },
    {
        "Front": "カラー",
        "Back": "collar,color,colour",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "からかう",
        "Back": "to ridicule,to tease,to banter with,to make fun of",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "空っぽ",
        "Back": "empty,vacant,hollow",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 261
    },
    {
        "Front": "かるた",
        "Back": "(n) playing cards (pt: carta)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "枯れる",
        "Back": "to wither,to die (plant),to be blasted (plant)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 262
    },
    {
        "Front": "カロリー",
        "Back": "calorie",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "かわいがる",
        "Back": "to love,to be affectionate",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "乾かす",
        "Back": "to dry (clothes, etc.),to desiccate",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 263
    },
    {
        "Front": "渇く",
        "Back": "to be thirsty",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 264
    },
    {
        "Front": "為替",
        "Back": "money order,exchange",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 265
    },
    {
        "Front": "瓦",
        "Back": "roof tile",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 266
    },
    {
        "Front": "代る",
        "Back": "(v5r,vi) to take the place of,to relieve,to be substituted for",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 267
    },
    {
        "Front": "間隔",
        "Back": "space,interval,SPC",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 268
    },
    {
        "Front": "換気",
        "Back": "ventilation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 269
    },
    {
        "Front": "感激",
        "Back": "deep emotion,impression,inspiration",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 270
    },
    {
        "Front": "関西",
        "Back": "",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 271
    },
    {
        "Front": "鑑賞",
        "Back": "appreciation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 272
    },
    {
        "Front": "感ずる",
        "Back": "to feel,to sense",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 273
    },
    {
        "Front": "間接",
        "Back": "indirection,indirectness",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 274
    },
    {
        "Front": "乾燥",
        "Back": "dry,arid,insipid,dehydrated",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 275
    },
    {
        "Front": "感想",
        "Back": "impressions,thoughts",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 276
    },
    {
        "Front": "観測",
        "Back": "observation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 277
    },
    {
        "Front": "寒帯",
        "Back": "frigid zone",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 278
    },
    {
        "Front": "勘違い",
        "Back": "misunderstanding,wrong guess",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 280
    },
    {
        "Front": "官庁",
        "Back": "government office,authorities",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 279
    },
    {
        "Front": "缶詰",
        "Back": "packing (in cans),canning,canned goods,tin can",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 281
    },
    {
        "Front": "乾電池",
        "Back": "dry cell,battery",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 282
    },
    {
        "Front": "関東",
        "Back": "eastern half of Japan, including Tokyo",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 283
    },
    {
        "Front": "観念",
        "Back": "(1) idea,notion,conception,(2) sense (e.g. of duty)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 284
    },
    {
        "Front": "乾杯",
        "Back": "toast (drink)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 285
    },
    {
        "Front": "看板",
        "Back": "sign,signboard,doorplate,poster",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 286
    },
    {
        "Front": "看病",
        "Back": "nursing (a patient)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 287
    },
    {
        "Front": "冠",
        "Back": "crown,diadem,first,best",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 288
    },
    {
        "Front": "漢和",
        "Back": "Chinese Character-Japanese (e.g. dictionary)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 289
    },
    {
        "Front": "気圧",
        "Back": "atmospheric pressure",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 290
    },
    {
        "Front": "器械",
        "Back": "instrument",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 291
    },
    {
        "Front": "着替え",
        "Back": "changing clothes,change of clothes",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 292
    },
    {
        "Front": "機関車",
        "Back": "locomotive,engine",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 293
    },
    {
        "Front": "飢饉",
        "Back": "famine",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 294
    },
    {
        "Front": "器具",
        "Back": "utensil",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 295
    },
    {
        "Front": "期限",
        "Back": "term,period",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 296
    },
    {
        "Front": "記号",
        "Back": "symbol,code",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 297
    },
    {
        "Front": "刻む",
        "Back": "to mince,to carve,to engrave",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 298
    },
    {
        "Front": "儀式",
        "Back": "ceremony,rite,ritual,service",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 299
    },
    {
        "Front": "基準",
        "Back": "standard,basis,criteria,norm",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 300
    },
    {
        "Front": "規準",
        "Back": "standard,basis,criteria,norm",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 301
    },
    {
        "Front": "起床",
        "Back": "rising,getting out of bed",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 302
    },
    {
        "Front": "着せる",
        "Back": "to put on clothes",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 303
    },
    {
        "Front": "基礎",
        "Back": "foundation,basis",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 304
    },
    {
        "Front": "気体",
        "Back": "vapour,gas",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 305
    },
    {
        "Front": "基地",
        "Back": "base",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 306
    },
    {
        "Front": "きっかけ",
        "Back": "chance,start,cue,excuse",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ぎっしり",
        "Back": "tightly,fully",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "基盤",
        "Back": "foundation,basis",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 307
    },
    {
        "Front": "客席",
        "Back": "guest seating",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 308
    },
    {
        "Front": "客間",
        "Back": "parlor,guest room",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 309
    },
    {
        "Front": "ギャング",
        "Back": "gang",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "キャンパス",
        "Back": "campus",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "休業",
        "Back": "closed (e.g. store),business suspended,shutdown,holiday",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 310
    },
    {
        "Front": "休講",
        "Back": "lecture cancelled",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 311
    },
    {
        "Front": "休息",
        "Back": "rest,relief,relaxation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 312
    },
    {
        "Front": "給与",
        "Back": "allowance,grant,supply",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 313
    },
    {
        "Front": "休養",
        "Back": "rest,break,recreation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 314
    },
    {
        "Front": "清い",
        "Back": "clear,pure,noble",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 315
    },
    {
        "Front": "強化",
        "Back": "strengthen,intensify,reinforce,solidify",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 316
    },
    {
        "Front": "境界",
        "Back": "boundary",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 317
    },
    {
        "Front": "行事",
        "Back": "event,function",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 318
    },
    {
        "Front": "恐縮",
        "Back": "shame,very kind of you,sorry to trouble",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 319
    },
    {
        "Front": "教養",
        "Back": "culture,education,refinement,cultivation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 320
    },
    {
        "Front": "行列",
        "Back": "(1) line,procession,(2) matrix (math)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 321
    },
    {
        "Front": "漁業",
        "Back": "fishing (industry)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 322
    },
    {
        "Front": "曲線",
        "Back": "curve",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 323
    },
    {
        "Front": "規律",
        "Back": "order,rules,law",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 324
    },
    {
        "Front": "斬る",
        "Back": "(v5r) to behead,to murder",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 325
    },
    {
        "Front": "気を付ける",
        "Back": "to be careful,to pay attention,to take care",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 326
    },
    {
        "Front": "金魚",
        "Back": "goldfish",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 327
    },
    {
        "Front": "区域",
        "Back": "limits,boundary,domain,zone,sphere,territory",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 328
    },
    {
        "Front": "偶数",
        "Back": "even number",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 329
    },
    {
        "Front": "空想",
        "Back": "daydream,fantasy,fancy,vision",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 330
    },
    {
        "Front": "空中",
        "Back": "sky,air",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 331
    },
    {
        "Front": "クーラー",
        "Back": "cooler,air conditioner",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "釘",
        "Back": "nail",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 332
    },
    {
        "Front": "区切る",
        "Back": "to punctuate,to cut off,to mark off,to stop,to put an end to",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 333
    },
    {
        "Front": "櫛",
        "Back": "comb",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 334
    },
    {
        "Front": "くしゃみ",
        "Back": "sneeze",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "苦情",
        "Back": "complaint,troubles,objection",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 335
    },
    {
        "Front": "苦心",
        "Back": "pain,trouble",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 336
    },
    {
        "Front": "屑",
        "Back": "waste,scrap",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 337
    },
    {
        "Front": "崩す",
        "Back": "to destroy,to pull down,to make change (money)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 338
    },
    {
        "Front": "薬指",
        "Back": "ring finger",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 339
    },
    {
        "Front": "崩れる",
        "Back": "to collapse,to crumble",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 340
    },
    {
        "Front": "砕く",
        "Back": "to break,to smash",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 341
    },
    {
        "Front": "砕ける",
        "Back": "to break,to be broken",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 342
    },
    {
        "Front": "くたびれる",
        "Back": "to get tired,to wear out",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "くだらない",
        "Back": "good-for-nothing,stupid,trivial,worthless",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "下る",
        "Back": "to get down,to descend",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 343
    },
    {
        "Front": "唇",
        "Back": "lips",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 344
    },
    {
        "Front": "口紅",
        "Back": "lipstick",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 345
    },
    {
        "Front": "くっつく",
        "Back": "to adhere to,to keep close to",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "くっつける",
        "Back": "to attach",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "くどい",
        "Back": "verbose,importunate,heavy (taste)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "句読点",
        "Back": "punctuation marks",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 346
    },
    {
        "Front": "配る",
        "Back": "to distribute,to deliver",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 347
    },
    {
        "Front": "工夫",
        "Back": "labourer,worker",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 348
    },
    {
        "Front": "区分",
        "Back": "division,section,classification",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 349
    },
    {
        "Front": "組合せ",
        "Back": "combination",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 350
    },
    {
        "Front": "組み立てる",
        "Back": "to assemble,to set up,to construct",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 351
    },
    {
        "Front": "汲む",
        "Back": "(1) to draw (water),to dip,to scoop,to pump",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 352
    },
    {
        "Front": "酌む",
        "Back": "to serve sake",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 353
    },
    {
        "Front": "悔しい",
        "Back": "regrettable,mortifying,vexing",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 354
    },
    {
        "Front": "悔やむ",
        "Back": "to mourn",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 355
    },
    {
        "Front": "クリーニング",
        "Back": "cleaning,dry cleaning,laundry service",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "くるむ",
        "Back": "to be engulfed in,to be enveloped by,to wrap up",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "くれぐれも",
        "Back": "repeatedly,sincerely,earnestly",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "咥える",
        "Back": "",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 356
    },
    {
        "Front": "郡",
        "Back": "country,district",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 357
    },
    {
        "Front": "稽古",
        "Back": "practice,training,study",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 358
    },
    {
        "Front": "敬語",
        "Back": "honorific,term of respect",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 359
    },
    {
        "Front": "蛍光灯",
        "Back": "fluorescent lamp,person who is slow to react",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 360
    },
    {
        "Front": "形式",
        "Back": "form,formality,format,math expression",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 361
    },
    {
        "Front": "継続",
        "Back": "continuation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 362
    },
    {
        "Front": "毛糸",
        "Back": "knitting wool",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 363
    },
    {
        "Front": "経度",
        "Back": "longitude",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 364
    },
    {
        "Front": "系統",
        "Back": "system,family line,geological formation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 365
    },
    {
        "Front": "芸能",
        "Back": "public entertainment,accomplishments,attainments",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 366
    },
    {
        "Front": "競馬",
        "Back": "horse racing",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 367
    },
    {
        "Front": "警備",
        "Back": "defense,guard,policing,security",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 368
    },
    {
        "Front": "形容詞",
        "Back": "true adjective",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 369
    },
    {
        "Front": "形容動詞",
        "Back": "adjectival noun,quasi-adjective",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 370
    },
    {
        "Front": "外科",
        "Back": "surgical department",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 371
    },
    {
        "Front": "毛皮",
        "Back": "fur,skin,pelt",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 372
    },
    {
        "Front": "激増",
        "Back": "sudden increase",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 373
    },
    {
        "Front": "下車",
        "Back": "alighting,getting off",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 374
    },
    {
        "Front": "下旬",
        "Back": "month (last third of)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 375
    },
    {
        "Front": "下水",
        "Back": "drainage,sewage,ditch,gutter,sewerage",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 376
    },
    {
        "Front": "削る",
        "Back": "to cut down little by little,to take a percentage",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 377
    },
    {
        "Front": "桁",
        "Back": "column,beam,digit",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 378
    },
    {
        "Front": "下駄",
        "Back": "geta (Japanese footwear),wooden clogs",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 379
    },
    {
        "Front": "血圧",
        "Back": "blood pressure",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 380
    },
    {
        "Front": "血液",
        "Back": "blood",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 381
    },
    {
        "Front": "月給",
        "Back": "monthly salary",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 382
    },
    {
        "Front": "傑作",
        "Back": "masterpiece,best work,boner,blunder",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 383
    },
    {
        "Front": "月末",
        "Back": "end of the month",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 384
    },
    {
        "Front": "気配",
        "Back": "indication,market trend,worry",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 385
    },
    {
        "Front": "下品",
        "Back": "vulgarity,meanness,indecency,coarseness",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 386
    },
    {
        "Front": "煙い",
        "Back": "smoky",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 387
    },
    {
        "Front": "蹴る",
        "Back": "to kick",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 388
    },
    {
        "Front": "けれど/けれども",
        "Back": "but,however",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "険しい",
        "Back": "inaccessible place,sharp eyes",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 390
    },
    {
        "Front": "見学",
        "Back": "inspection,study by observation,field trip",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 391
    },
    {
        "Front": "謙虚",
        "Back": "modesty,humility",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 392
    },
    {
        "Front": "原稿",
        "Back": "manuscript,copy",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 393
    },
    {
        "Front": "原産",
        "Back": "place of origin,habitat",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 394
    },
    {
        "Front": "原始",
        "Back": "origin,primeval",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 395
    },
    {
        "Front": "研修",
        "Back": "training",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 396
    },
    {
        "Front": "厳重",
        "Back": "strict,rigour,severe,firm",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 397
    },
    {
        "Front": "謙遜",
        "Back": "humble,humility,modesty",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 398
    },
    {
        "Front": "県庁",
        "Back": "prefectural office",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 399
    },
    {
        "Front": "限度",
        "Back": "limit,bounds",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 400
    },
    {
        "Front": "現に",
        "Back": "actually,really",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 401
    },
    {
        "Front": "顕微鏡",
        "Back": "microscope",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 402
    },
    {
        "Front": "原理",
        "Back": "principle,theory,fundamental truth",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 403
    },
    {
        "Front": "原料",
        "Back": "raw materials",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 404
    },
    {
        "Front": "碁",
        "Back": "Go (board game of capturing territory)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 405
    },
    {
        "Front": "恋しい",
        "Back": "(1) dear,beloved,darling,(2) yearned for",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 406
    },
    {
        "Front": "請う",
        "Back": "to ask,to request",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 407
    },
    {
        "Front": "工員",
        "Back": "factory worker",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 408
    },
    {
        "Front": "強引",
        "Back": "overbearing,coercive,pushy,forcible,high-handed",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 409
    },
    {
        "Front": "公害",
        "Back": "public nuisance,pollution",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 410
    },
    {
        "Front": "高級",
        "Back": "high class,high grade",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 411
    },
    {
        "Front": "公共",
        "Back": "public,community,public service,society,communal",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 412
    },
    {
        "Front": "工芸",
        "Back": "industrial arts",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 413
    },
    {
        "Front": "孝行",
        "Back": "filial piety",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 414
    },
    {
        "Front": "交差",
        "Back": "cross",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 415
    },
    {
        "Front": "講師",
        "Back": "lecturer",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 416
    },
    {
        "Front": "工事",
        "Back": "construction work",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 417
    },
    {
        "Front": "公式",
        "Back": "formula,formality,official",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 418
    },
    {
        "Front": "口実",
        "Back": "excuse",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 419
    },
    {
        "Front": "こうして",
        "Back": "thus",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "校舎",
        "Back": "school building",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 421
    },
    {
        "Front": "公衆",
        "Back": "the public",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 422
    },
    {
        "Front": "香水",
        "Back": "perfume",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 423
    },
    {
        "Front": "公正",
        "Back": "justice,fairness,impartiality",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 424
    },
    {
        "Front": "功績",
        "Back": "achievements,merit,meritorious service,meritorious deed",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 425
    },
    {
        "Front": "光線",
        "Back": "beam,light ray",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 426
    },
    {
        "Front": "高層",
        "Back": "upper",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 427
    },
    {
        "Front": "構造",
        "Back": "structure,construction",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 428
    },
    {
        "Front": "交替",
        "Back": "alternation,change,relief,relay,shift",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 429
    },
    {
        "Front": "耕地",
        "Back": "arable land",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 430
    },
    {
        "Front": "交通機関",
        "Back": "transportation facilities",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 431
    },
    {
        "Front": "校庭",
        "Back": "campus",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 432
    },
    {
        "Front": "肯定",
        "Back": "positive,affirmation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 433
    },
    {
        "Front": "高度",
        "Back": "altitude,height,advanced",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 434
    },
    {
        "Front": "高等",
        "Back": "high class,high grade",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 435
    },
    {
        "Front": "合同",
        "Back": "combination,incorporation,union,amalgamation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 436
    },
    {
        "Front": "後輩",
        "Back": "junior (at work or school)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 437
    },
    {
        "Front": "公表",
        "Back": "official announcement,proclamation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 438
    },
    {
        "Front": "鉱物",
        "Back": "mineral",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 439
    },
    {
        "Front": "公務",
        "Back": "official business,public business",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 440
    },
    {
        "Front": "項目",
        "Back": "item",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 441
    },
    {
        "Front": "紅葉",
        "Back": "(1) (Japanese) maple",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 442
    },
    {
        "Front": "合理",
        "Back": "rational",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 443
    },
    {
        "Front": "交流",
        "Back": "alternating current,intercourse,(cultural) exchange,intermingling",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 444
    },
    {
        "Front": "合流",
        "Back": "confluence,union,linking up,merge",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 445
    },
    {
        "Front": "効力",
        "Back": "effect,efficacy,validity,potency",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 446
    },
    {
        "Front": "超える",
        "Back": "to exceed,to cross over,to cross",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 447
    },
    {
        "Front": "コース",
        "Back": "course",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "コーラス",
        "Back": "chorus",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "焦がす",
        "Back": "to burn,to scorch,to singe,to char",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 448
    },
    {
        "Front": "国王",
        "Back": "king",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 449
    },
    {
        "Front": "国籍",
        "Back": "nationality",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 450
    },
    {
        "Front": "国立",
        "Back": "national",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 451
    },
    {
        "Front": "ごくろうさま",
        "Back": "Thank you very much for your....",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "焦げる",
        "Back": "to burn,to be burned",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 452
    },
    {
        "Front": "凍える",
        "Back": "to freeze,to be chilled,to be frozen",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 453
    },
    {
        "Front": "心当たり",
        "Back": "having some knowledge of,happening to know",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 454
    },
    {
        "Front": "心得る",
        "Back": "to be informed,to have thorough knowledge",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 455
    },
    {
        "Front": "腰掛け",
        "Back": "seat,bench",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 456
    },
    {
        "Front": "腰掛ける",
        "Back": "to sit (down)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 457
    },
    {
        "Front": "五十音",
        "Back": "the Japanese syllabary",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 458
    },
    {
        "Front": "胡椒",
        "Back": "pepper",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 459
    },
    {
        "Front": "こしらえる",
        "Back": "to make,to manufacture",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "超す",
        "Back": "to cross,to pass,to tide over",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 460
    },
    {
        "Front": "擦る",
        "Back": "to rub,to chafe,to file,to frost (glass),to strike (match)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 461
    },
    {
        "Front": "ごぞんじですか",
        "Back": "",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "個体",
        "Back": "an individual",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 462
    },
    {
        "Front": "御馳走",
        "Back": "feast,treating (someone)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 463
    },
    {
        "Front": "ごちそうさま",
        "Back": "feast",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "こちらこそ",
        "Back": "it is I who should say so",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "小遣い",
        "Back": "personal expenses,pocket money,spending money,incidental expenses,allowance",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 464
    },
    {
        "Front": "コック",
        "Back": "(1) cook (nl:),(2) tap,spigot,faucet,cock",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "こっそり",
        "Back": "stealthily,secretly",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "古典",
        "Back": "old book,classics,classic",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 465
    },
    {
        "Front": "琴",
        "Back": "Koto (Japanese harp)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 466
    },
    {
        "Front": "言付ける",
        "Back": "to send word,to send a message",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 467
    },
    {
        "Front": "言葉遣い",
        "Back": "speech,expression,wording",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 468
    },
    {
        "Front": "こないだ",
        "Back": "the other day,lately,recently",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "御無沙汰",
        "Back": "not writing or contacting for a while",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 469
    },
    {
        "Front": "こぼす",
        "Back": "to spill",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "こぼれる",
        "Back": "to overflow,to spill",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "塵芥",
        "Back": "trash,rubbish",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 470
    },
    {
        "Front": "ゴム",
        "Back": "gum,rubber,eraser",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "御免",
        "Back": "your pardon,declining (something),dismissal,permission",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 471
    },
    {
        "Front": "ごめんください",
        "Back": "May I come in?",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "小指",
        "Back": "little finger",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 472
    },
    {
        "Front": "こらえる",
        "Back": "to bear,to stand,to endure,to put up with",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "娯楽",
        "Back": "pleasure,amusement",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 473
    },
    {
        "Front": "御覧",
        "Back": "(hon) look,inspection,try",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 474
    },
    {
        "Front": "コレクション",
        "Back": "(1) collection,(2) correction",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "転がす",
        "Back": "to roll",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 475
    },
    {
        "Front": "転がる",
        "Back": "to roll,to tumble",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 476
    },
    {
        "Front": "紺",
        "Back": "navy blue,deep blue",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 477
    },
    {
        "Front": "コンクール",
        "Back": "contest (fr: concours)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "コンクリート",
        "Back": "concrete",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "混合",
        "Back": "mixing,mixture",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 478
    },
    {
        "Front": "コンセント",
        "Back": "(1) consent,(2) concentric",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "献立",
        "Back": "menu,program,schedule",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 479
    },
    {
        "Front": "こんばんは",
        "Back": "good evening",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "サークル",
        "Back": "circle,sports club (i.e. at a company)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "在学",
        "Back": "(enrolled) in school",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 480
    },
    {
        "Front": "再三",
        "Back": "again and again,repeatedly",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 481
    },
    {
        "Front": "祭日",
        "Back": "national holiday,festival day",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 482
    },
    {
        "Front": "催促",
        "Back": "request,demand,claim,urge (action),press for",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 483
    },
    {
        "Front": "採点",
        "Back": "marking,grading,looking over",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 484
    },
    {
        "Front": "災難",
        "Back": "calamity,misfortune",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 485
    },
    {
        "Front": "裁縫",
        "Back": "sewing",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 486
    },
    {
        "Front": "材木",
        "Back": "lumber,timber",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 487
    },
    {
        "Front": "サイレン",
        "Back": "siren",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "逆さ",
        "Back": "reverse,inversion,upside down",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 488
    },
    {
        "Front": "逆様",
        "Back": "inversion,upside down",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 489
    },
    {
        "Front": "捜す",
        "Back": "to search,to seek,to look for",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 490
    },
    {
        "Front": "遡る",
        "Back": "to go back,to go upstream,to make retroactive",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 491
    },
    {
        "Front": "酒場",
        "Back": "bar,bar-room",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 492
    },
    {
        "Front": "さきおととい",
        "Back": "two days before yesterday",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "先程",
        "Back": "some time ago",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 493
    },
    {
        "Front": "裂く",
        "Back": "to tear,to split",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 494
    },
    {
        "Front": "索引",
        "Back": "index,indices",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 495
    },
    {
        "Front": "作者",
        "Back": "author,authoress",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 496
    },
    {
        "Front": "削除",
        "Back": "elimination,cancellation,deletion,erasure",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 497
    },
    {
        "Front": "作成",
        "Back": "frame,draw up,make,producing",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 498
    },
    {
        "Front": "作製",
        "Back": "manufacture",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 499
    },
    {
        "Front": "探る",
        "Back": "to search,to look for,to sound out",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 500
    },
    {
        "Front": "囁く",
        "Back": "to whisper,to murmur",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 501
    },
    {
        "Front": "刺さる",
        "Back": "to stick,to be stuck",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 502
    },
    {
        "Front": "匙",
        "Back": "spoon",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 503
    },
    {
        "Front": "座敷",
        "Back": "tatami room",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 504
    },
    {
        "Front": "差し支え",
        "Back": "hindrance,impediment",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 505
    },
    {
        "Front": "差し引き",
        "Back": "deduction,subtraction,balance,ebb and flow,rise and fall",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 506
    },
    {
        "Front": "刺身",
        "Back": "sliced raw fish",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 507
    },
    {
        "Front": "刺す",
        "Back": "to pierce,to stab,to prick,to thrust",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 508
    },
    {
        "Front": "挿す",
        "Back": "to insert,to put in,to graft,to wear in belt",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 509
    },
    {
        "Front": "注す",
        "Back": "to pour (drink),to serve (drinks)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 510
    },
    {
        "Front": "射す",
        "Back": "to shine,to strike",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 511
    },
    {
        "Front": "流石",
        "Back": "clever,adept,good,expectations,as one would expect",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 512
    },
    {
        "Front": "撮影",
        "Back": "photographing",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 513
    },
    {
        "Front": "雑音",
        "Back": "noise (jarring, grating)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 514
    },
    {
        "Front": "さっさと",
        "Back": "quickly",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "早速",
        "Back": "at once,immediately,without delay,promptly",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 515
    },
    {
        "Front": "錆",
        "Back": "rust (colour)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 516
    },
    {
        "Front": "錆びる",
        "Back": "to rust,to become rusty",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 517
    },
    {
        "Front": "座布団",
        "Back": "cushion (Japanese)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 518
    },
    {
        "Front": "冷ます",
        "Back": "to cool,to dampen,to let cool",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 519
    },
    {
        "Front": "妨げる",
        "Back": "to disturb,to prevent",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 520
    },
    {
        "Front": "冷める",
        "Back": "to become cool,to wear off,to abate,to subside",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 521
    },
    {
        "Front": "さようなら",
        "Back": "good-bye",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "再来月",
        "Back": "month after next",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 522
    },
    {
        "Front": "再来週",
        "Back": "week after next",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 523
    },
    {
        "Front": "再来年",
        "Back": "year after next",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 524
    },
    {
        "Front": "サラリーマン",
        "Back": "salary man,company employee",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "騒がしい",
        "Back": "noisy",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 525
    },
    {
        "Front": "さわやか",
        "Back": "fresh,refreshing,invigorating",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "三角",
        "Back": "triangle,triangular",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 526
    },
    {
        "Front": "算数",
        "Back": "arithmetic",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 527
    },
    {
        "Front": "酸性",
        "Back": "acidity",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 528
    },
    {
        "Front": "産地",
        "Back": "producing area",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 529
    },
    {
        "Front": "サンプル",
        "Back": "sample",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "山林",
        "Back": "mountain forest,mountains and forest",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 530
    },
    {
        "Front": "仕上がる",
        "Back": "to be finished",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 531
    },
    {
        "Front": "しあさって",
        "Back": "two days after tomorrow",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "シーズン",
        "Back": "season (sporting)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "シーツ",
        "Back": "sheet",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "寺院",
        "Back": "temple",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 532
    },
    {
        "Front": "しいんと",
        "Back": "silent (as the grave),(deathly) quiet",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "自衛",
        "Back": "self-defense",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 534
    },
    {
        "Front": "塩辛い",
        "Back": "salty (taste)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 535
    },
    {
        "Front": "司会",
        "Back": "chairmanship",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 536
    },
    {
        "Front": "四角",
        "Back": "square",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 537
    },
    {
        "Front": "四角い",
        "Back": "square",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 538
    },
    {
        "Front": "時間割",
        "Back": "timetable,schedule",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 539
    },
    {
        "Front": "四季",
        "Back": "four seasons",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 540
    },
    {
        "Front": "敷地",
        "Back": "site",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 541
    },
    {
        "Front": "至急",
        "Back": "urgent,pressing",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 542
    },
    {
        "Front": "敷く",
        "Back": "to spread out,to lay out",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 543
    },
    {
        "Front": "茂る",
        "Back": "to grow thick,to luxuriate,to be luxurious",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 544
    },
    {
        "Front": "持参",
        "Back": "bringing,taking,carrying",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 545
    },
    {
        "Front": "磁石",
        "Back": "magnet",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 546
    },
    {
        "Front": "四捨五入",
        "Back": "rounding up (fractions)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 547
    },
    {
        "Front": "始終",
        "Back": "continuously,from beginning to end",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 548
    },
    {
        "Front": "自習",
        "Back": "self-study",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 549
    },
    {
        "Front": "静まる",
        "Back": "to quieten down,to calm down,to subside",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 550
    },
    {
        "Front": "姿勢",
        "Back": "attitude,posture",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 551
    },
    {
        "Front": "自然科学",
        "Back": "natural science",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 552
    },
    {
        "Front": "時速",
        "Back": "speed (per hour)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 553
    },
    {
        "Front": "子孫",
        "Back": "descendants,posterity,offspring",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 554
    },
    {
        "Front": "死体",
        "Back": "corpse",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 555
    },
    {
        "Front": "下書き",
        "Back": "rough copy,draft",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 556
    },
    {
        "Front": "下町",
        "Back": "Shitamachi,lower parts of town",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 557
    },
    {
        "Front": "自治",
        "Back": "self-government,autonomy",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 558
    },
    {
        "Front": "実感",
        "Back": "feelings (actual, true)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 559
    },
    {
        "Front": "湿気",
        "Back": "moisture,humidity,dampness",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 560
    },
    {
        "Front": "しつこい",
        "Back": "insistent,obstinate",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "実習",
        "Back": "practice,training",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 561
    },
    {
        "Front": "実績",
        "Back": "achievements,actual results",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 562
    },
    {
        "Front": "湿度",
        "Back": "level of humidity",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 563
    },
    {
        "Front": "執筆",
        "Back": "writing",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 564
    },
    {
        "Front": "実物",
        "Back": "real thing,original",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 565
    },
    {
        "Front": "しっぽ",
        "Back": "tail (animal)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "実用",
        "Back": "practical use,utility",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 566
    },
    {
        "Front": "実力",
        "Back": "merit,efficiency,arms,force",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 567
    },
    {
        "Front": "実例",
        "Back": "example,illustration",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 568
    },
    {
        "Front": "失恋",
        "Back": "disappointed love,broken heart,unrequited love,be lovelorn",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 569
    },
    {
        "Front": "指定",
        "Back": "designation,specification,assignment,pointing at",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 570
    },
    {
        "Front": "私鉄",
        "Back": "private railway",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 571
    },
    {
        "Front": "児童",
        "Back": "children,juvenile",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 572
    },
    {
        "Front": "縛る",
        "Back": "to tie,to bind",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 573
    },
    {
        "Front": "地盤",
        "Back": "(the) ground",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 574
    },
    {
        "Front": "しびれる",
        "Back": "to become numb,to go to sleep (i.e., a limb)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "紙幣",
        "Back": "paper money,notes,bills",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 575
    },
    {
        "Front": "しぼむ",
        "Back": "to wither,to fade (away),to shrivel,to wilt",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "絞る",
        "Back": "to press,to wring,to squeeze",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 576
    },
    {
        "Front": "縞",
        "Back": "stripe",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 577
    },
    {
        "Front": "地味",
        "Back": "plain,simple",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 578
    },
    {
        "Front": "しみじみ",
        "Back": "keenly,deeply,heartily",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "氏名",
        "Back": "full name,identity",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 579
    },
    {
        "Front": "締切",
        "Back": "closing,cut-off,end,deadline,Closed,No Entrance",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 580
    },
    {
        "Front": "締め切る",
        "Back": "to shut up",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 581
    },
    {
        "Front": "湿る",
        "Back": "to be wet,to become wet,to be damp",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 582
    },
    {
        "Front": "ジャーナリスト",
        "Back": "journalist",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "社会科学",
        "Back": "social science",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 583
    },
    {
        "Front": "しゃがむ",
        "Back": "to squat",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "蛇口",
        "Back": "faucet,tap",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 584
    },
    {
        "Front": "弱点",
        "Back": "weak point,weakness",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 585
    },
    {
        "Front": "車庫",
        "Back": "garage,car shed",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 586
    },
    {
        "Front": "車掌",
        "Back": "(train) conductor",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 587
    },
    {
        "Front": "写生",
        "Back": "sketching,drawing from nature",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 588
    },
    {
        "Front": "社説",
        "Back": "editorial,leading article",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 589
    },
    {
        "Front": "しゃっくり",
        "Back": "hiccough,hiccup",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "シャッター",
        "Back": "shutter",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "しゃぶる",
        "Back": "to suck,to chew",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "車輪",
        "Back": "(car) wheel",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 590
    },
    {
        "Front": "洒落",
        "Back": "joke,pun,witticism",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 591
    },
    {
        "Front": "じゃんけん",
        "Back": "(n) rock-scissors-paper game",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "集会",
        "Back": "meeting,assembly",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 592
    },
    {
        "Front": "住居",
        "Back": "dwelling,house,residence,address",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 593
    },
    {
        "Front": "集金",
        "Back": "money collection",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 594
    },
    {
        "Front": "集合",
        "Back": "gathering,assembly,meeting,set (math)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 595
    },
    {
        "Front": "習字",
        "Back": "penmanship",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 596
    },
    {
        "Front": "修繕",
        "Back": "repair,mending",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 597
    },
    {
        "Front": "重体",
        "Back": "seriously ill,serious condition,critical state",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 598
    },
    {
        "Front": "じゅうたん",
        "Back": "carpet",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "終点",
        "Back": "terminus,last stop (e.g train)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 600
    },
    {
        "Front": "重点",
        "Back": "important point,lay stress on,colon,emphasis",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 601
    },
    {
        "Front": "就任",
        "Back": "inauguration,assumption of office",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 602
    },
    {
        "Front": "周辺",
        "Back": "circumference,outskirts,environs,(computer) peripheral",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 603
    },
    {
        "Front": "重役",
        "Back": "director,high executive",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 604
    },
    {
        "Front": "終了",
        "Back": "end,close,termination",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 605
    },
    {
        "Front": "重量",
        "Back": "(1) weight,(2) heavyweight boxer",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 606
    },
    {
        "Front": "重力",
        "Back": "gravity",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 607
    },
    {
        "Front": "熟語",
        "Back": "idiom,idiomatic phrase,kanji compound",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 608
    },
    {
        "Front": "祝日",
        "Back": "national holiday",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 609
    },
    {
        "Front": "縮小",
        "Back": "reduction,curtailment",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 610
    },
    {
        "Front": "受験",
        "Back": "taking an examination",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 611
    },
    {
        "Front": "主語",
        "Back": "(gram) subject",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 612
    },
    {
        "Front": "出勤",
        "Back": "going to work,at work",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 613
    },
    {
        "Front": "述語",
        "Back": "predicate",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 614
    },
    {
        "Front": "出張",
        "Back": "official tour,business trip",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 615
    },
    {
        "Front": "寿命",
        "Back": "life span",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 616
    },
    {
        "Front": "主役",
        "Back": "leading part,leading actor (actress)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 617
    },
    {
        "Front": "受話器",
        "Back": "(telephone) receiver",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 618
    },
    {
        "Front": "循環",
        "Back": "circulation,rotation,cycle",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 619
    },
    {
        "Front": "巡査",
        "Back": "police,policeman",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 620
    },
    {
        "Front": "順々",
        "Back": "in order,in turn",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 621
    },
    {
        "Front": "順序",
        "Back": "order,sequence,procedure",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 622
    },
    {
        "Front": "純情",
        "Back": "pure heart,naivete,self-sacrificing devotion",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 623
    },
    {
        "Front": "純粋",
        "Back": "pure,true,genuine,unmixed",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 624
    },
    {
        "Front": "消化",
        "Back": "digestion",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 625
    },
    {
        "Front": "小学生",
        "Back": "grade school student",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 626
    },
    {
        "Front": "しょうがない",
        "Back": "",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "将棋",
        "Back": "Japanese chess",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 627
    },
    {
        "Front": "蒸気",
        "Back": "steam,vapour",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 628
    },
    {
        "Front": "定規",
        "Back": "(measuring) ruler",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 629
    },
    {
        "Front": "上級",
        "Back": "advanced level,high grade,senior",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 630
    },
    {
        "Front": "商業",
        "Back": "commerce,trade,business",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 631
    },
    {
        "Front": "消極的",
        "Back": "passive",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 632
    },
    {
        "Front": "賞金",
        "Back": "prize,monetary award",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 633
    },
    {
        "Front": "上下",
        "Back": "high and low,up and down,unloading and loading,praising and blaming",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 634
    },
    {
        "Front": "障子",
        "Back": "paper sliding door",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 635
    },
    {
        "Front": "商社",
        "Back": "trading company,firm",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 636
    },
    {
        "Front": "乗車",
        "Back": "taking a train,entraining",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 637
    },
    {
        "Front": "上旬",
        "Back": "first 10 days of month",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 638
    },
    {
        "Front": "生ずる",
        "Back": "to cause,to arise,to be generated",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 639
    },
    {
        "Front": "小数",
        "Back": "fraction (part of),decimal",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 640
    },
    {
        "Front": "商店",
        "Back": "shop,business firm",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 641
    },
    {
        "Front": "焦点",
        "Back": "focus,point",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 642
    },
    {
        "Front": "消毒",
        "Back": "disinfection,sterilization",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 643
    },
    {
        "Front": "勝敗",
        "Back": "victory or defeat,issue (of battle)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 644
    },
    {
        "Front": "蒸発",
        "Back": "evaporation,unexplained disappearance",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 645
    },
    {
        "Front": "賞品",
        "Back": "prize,trophy",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 646
    },
    {
        "Front": "勝負",
        "Back": "victory or defeat,match,contest,game,bout",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 647
    },
    {
        "Front": "小便",
        "Back": "(col) urine,piss",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 648
    },
    {
        "Front": "消防署",
        "Back": "fire station",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 649
    },
    {
        "Front": "正味",
        "Back": "net (weight)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 650
    },
    {
        "Front": "正面",
        "Back": "the front,honesty",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 651
    },
    {
        "Front": "消耗",
        "Back": "exhaustion,consumption",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 652
    },
    {
        "Front": "醤油",
        "Back": "soy sauce",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 653
    },
    {
        "Front": "省略",
        "Back": "omission,abbreviation,abridgment",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 654
    },
    {
        "Front": "初級",
        "Back": "elementary level",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 655
    },
    {
        "Front": "助教授",
        "Back": "assistant professor",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 656
    },
    {
        "Front": "食塩",
        "Back": "table salt",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 657
    },
    {
        "Front": "職人",
        "Back": "worker,mechanic,artisan,craftsman",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 658
    },
    {
        "Front": "初旬",
        "Back": "first 10 days of the month",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 659
    },
    {
        "Front": "書籍",
        "Back": "book,publication",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 660
    },
    {
        "Front": "食器",
        "Back": "tableware",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 661
    },
    {
        "Front": "ショップ",
        "Back": "a shop",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "書店",
        "Back": "bookshop",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 662
    },
    {
        "Front": "書道",
        "Back": "calligraphy",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 663
    },
    {
        "Front": "白髪",
        "Back": "white or grey hair,trendy hair bleaching",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 664
    },
    {
        "Front": "知合い",
        "Back": "acquaintance",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 665
    },
    {
        "Front": "シリーズ",
        "Back": "series",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "私立",
        "Back": "private (establishment)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 666
    },
    {
        "Front": "資料",
        "Back": "materials,data",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 667
    },
    {
        "Front": "汁",
        "Back": "juice,sap,soup,broth",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 668
    },
    {
        "Front": "素人",
        "Back": "amateur,novice",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 669
    },
    {
        "Front": "芯",
        "Back": "core,heart,wick,marrow",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 670
    },
    {
        "Front": "新幹線",
        "Back": "bullet train (very high speed),shinkansen",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 671
    },
    {
        "Front": "真空",
        "Back": "vacuum,hollow,empty",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 672
    },
    {
        "Front": "信ずる",
        "Back": "to believe,to believe in,to place trust in",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 673
    },
    {
        "Front": "心身",
        "Back": "mind and body",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 674
    },
    {
        "Front": "申請",
        "Back": "application,request,petition",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 675
    },
    {
        "Front": "人造",
        "Back": "man-made,synthetic,artificial",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 676
    },
    {
        "Front": "寝台",
        "Back": "bed,couch",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 677
    },
    {
        "Front": "診断",
        "Back": "diagnosis",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 678
    },
    {
        "Front": "侵入",
        "Back": "penetration,invasion,raid,aggression,trespass",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 679
    },
    {
        "Front": "人文科学",
        "Back": "social sciences,humanities",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 680
    },
    {
        "Front": "人命",
        "Back": "(human) life",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 681
    },
    {
        "Front": "深夜",
        "Back": "late at night",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 682
    },
    {
        "Front": "森林",
        "Back": "forest,woods",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 683
    },
    {
        "Front": "親類",
        "Back": "relation,kin",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 684
    },
    {
        "Front": "針路",
        "Back": "course,direction,compass bearing",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 685
    },
    {
        "Front": "神話",
        "Back": "myth,legend",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 686
    },
    {
        "Front": "酢",
        "Back": "vinegar",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 687
    },
    {
        "Front": "水産",
        "Back": "marine products,fisheries",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 688
    },
    {
        "Front": "炊事",
        "Back": "cooking,culinary arts",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 689
    },
    {
        "Front": "水蒸気",
        "Back": "water vapour,steam",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 690
    },
    {
        "Front": "水素",
        "Back": "hydrogen",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 691
    },
    {
        "Front": "垂直",
        "Back": "vertical,perpendicular",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 692
    },
    {
        "Front": "推定",
        "Back": "presumption,assumption,estimation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 693
    },
    {
        "Front": "水滴",
        "Back": "drop of water",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 694
    },
    {
        "Front": "水筒",
        "Back": "canteen,flask,water bottle",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 695
    },
    {
        "Front": "随筆",
        "Back": "essays,miscellaneous writings",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 696
    },
    {
        "Front": "水分",
        "Back": "moisture",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 697
    },
    {
        "Front": "水平",
        "Back": "water level,horizon",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 698
    },
    {
        "Front": "水平線",
        "Back": "horizon",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 699
    },
    {
        "Front": "水曜",
        "Back": "Wednesday",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 700
    },
    {
        "Front": "ずうずうしい",
        "Back": "impudent,shameless",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ずうっと",
        "Back": "",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "末っ子",
        "Back": "youngest child",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 701
    },
    {
        "Front": "スカーフ",
        "Back": "scarf",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "図鑑",
        "Back": "picture book",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 702
    },
    {
        "Front": "杉",
        "Back": "Japanese cedar",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 703
    },
    {
        "Front": "好き嫌い",
        "Back": "likes and dislikes,taste",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 704
    },
    {
        "Front": "好き好き",
        "Back": "matter of taste",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 705
    },
    {
        "Front": "透き通る",
        "Back": "to be(come) transparent",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 706
    },
    {
        "Front": "隙間",
        "Back": "crevice,crack,gap,opening",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 707
    },
    {
        "Front": "スクール",
        "Back": "school",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "すくなくとも",
        "Back": "at least",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "図形",
        "Back": "figure",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 708
    },
    {
        "Front": "スケジュール",
        "Back": "schedule",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "鈴",
        "Back": "bell",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 709
    },
    {
        "Front": "涼む",
        "Back": "to cool oneself,to cool off,to enjoy evening cool",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 710
    },
    {
        "Front": "スタート",
        "Back": "start",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "スチュワーデス",
        "Back": "stewardess",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "すっきり",
        "Back": "shapely,clear,neat",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "すっぱい",
        "Back": "sour,acid",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ステージ",
        "Back": "(1) stage,(2) performance",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "棄てる",
        "Back": "",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 711
    },
    {
        "Front": "ストッキング",
        "Back": "stockings",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ストップ",
        "Back": "stop",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "素直",
        "Back": "obedient,meek,docile,unaffected",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 712
    },
    {
        "Front": "頭脳",
        "Back": "head,brains,intellect",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 713
    },
    {
        "Front": "スピーカー",
        "Back": "speaker",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "図表",
        "Back": "chart,diagram,graph",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 714
    },
    {
        "Front": "スマート",
        "Back": "smart,stylish,slim",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "住まい",
        "Back": "dwelling,house,residence,address",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 715
    },
    {
        "Front": "すまない",
        "Back": "sorry (phrase)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "墨",
        "Back": "ink",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 716
    },
    {
        "Front": "澄む",
        "Back": "to clear (e.g. weather),to become transparent",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 717
    },
    {
        "Front": "清む",
        "Back": "",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 718
    },
    {
        "Front": "相撲",
        "Back": "sumo wrestling",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 719
    },
    {
        "Front": "スライド",
        "Back": "slide",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ずらす",
        "Back": "to put off,to delay",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ずらり",
        "Back": "",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "掏摸",
        "Back": "pickpocket",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 720
    },
    {
        "Front": "刷る",
        "Back": "to print",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 721
    },
    {
        "Front": "狡い",
        "Back": "sly,cunning",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 722
    },
    {
        "Front": "すれちがう",
        "Back": "to pass by one another,to disagree",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "滑れる",
        "Back": "",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 723
    },
    {
        "Front": "寸法",
        "Back": "measurement,size,dimension",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 724
    },
    {
        "Front": "姓",
        "Back": "surname,family name",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 725
    },
    {
        "Front": "税関",
        "Back": "customs house",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 726
    },
    {
        "Front": "製作",
        "Back": "manufacture,production",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 727
    },
    {
        "Front": "制作",
        "Back": "work (film, book)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 728
    },
    {
        "Front": "性質",
        "Back": "nature,property,disposition",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 729
    },
    {
        "Front": "清書",
        "Back": "clean copy",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 730
    },
    {
        "Front": "青少年",
        "Back": "youth,young person",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 731
    },
    {
        "Front": "整数",
        "Back": "integer",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 732
    },
    {
        "Front": "清掃",
        "Back": "cleaning",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 733
    },
    {
        "Front": "生存",
        "Back": "existence,being,survival",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 734
    },
    {
        "Front": "生長",
        "Back": "growth,increment",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 735
    },
    {
        "Front": "政党",
        "Back": "(member of) political party",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 736
    },
    {
        "Front": "生年月日",
        "Back": "birth date",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 737
    },
    {
        "Front": "性能",
        "Back": "ability,efficiency",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 738
    },
    {
        "Front": "整備",
        "Back": "adjustment,completion,consolidation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 739
    },
    {
        "Front": "成分",
        "Back": "ingredient,component,composition",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 740
    },
    {
        "Front": "性別",
        "Back": "distinction by sex,sex,gender",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 741
    },
    {
        "Front": "正方形",
        "Back": "square",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 742
    },
    {
        "Front": "正門",
        "Back": "main gate,main entrance",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 743
    },
    {
        "Front": "成立",
        "Back": "coming into existence,arrangements,establishment,completion",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 744
    },
    {
        "Front": "西暦",
        "Back": "Christian Era,anno domini (A.D.)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 745
    },
    {
        "Front": "背負う",
        "Back": "to be burdened with,to carry on back or shoulder",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 746
    },
    {
        "Front": "赤道",
        "Back": "equator",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 747
    },
    {
        "Front": "折角",
        "Back": "with trouble,at great pains,long-awaited",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 748
    },
    {
        "Front": "接近",
        "Back": "getting closer,drawing nearer,approaching",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 749
    },
    {
        "Front": "石鹸",
        "Back": "soap",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 750
    },
    {
        "Front": "接する",
        "Back": "to come in contact with,to connect,to attend,to receive",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 751
    },
    {
        "Front": "せっせと",
        "Back": "",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "接続",
        "Back": "(1) connection,union,join,link,(2) changing trains",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 752
    },
    {
        "Front": "瀬戸物",
        "Back": "earthenware,crockery,china",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 753
    },
    {
        "Front": "ぜひとも",
        "Back": "by all means (with sense of not taking no for an answer)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "迫る",
        "Back": "to draw near,to press",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 754
    },
    {
        "Front": "ゼミ",
        "Back": "(n) seminar",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "せめて",
        "Back": "offense,method of attack",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "攻める",
        "Back": "to attack,to assault",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 755
    },
    {
        "Front": "セメント",
        "Back": "cement",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "栓",
        "Back": "stopper,cork,stopcock",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 756
    },
    {
        "Front": "前後",
        "Back": "around,throughout,front and back,before and behind,before and after",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 757
    },
    {
        "Front": "洗剤",
        "Back": "detergent,washing material",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 758
    },
    {
        "Front": "全集",
        "Back": "complete works",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 759
    },
    {
        "Front": "全身",
        "Back": "the whole body,full-length (portrait)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 760
    },
    {
        "Front": "扇子",
        "Back": "folding fan",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 761
    },
    {
        "Front": "専制",
        "Back": "despotism,autocracy",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 762
    },
    {
        "Front": "先々月",
        "Back": "month before last",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 763
    },
    {
        "Front": "先々週",
        "Back": "",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 764
    },
    {
        "Front": "先祖",
        "Back": "ancestor",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 765
    },
    {
        "Front": "先端",
        "Back": "pointed end,tip,fine point",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 766
    },
    {
        "Front": "センチ",
        "Back": "centimeter,centi-,10^-2",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "宣伝",
        "Back": "propaganda,publicity",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 767
    },
    {
        "Front": "先頭",
        "Back": "head,lead,vanguard,first",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 768
    },
    {
        "Front": "全般",
        "Back": "(the) whole,universal,wholly,general",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 769
    },
    {
        "Front": "扇風機",
        "Back": "electric fan",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 770
    },
    {
        "Front": "線路",
        "Back": "line,track,roadbed",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 771
    },
    {
        "Front": "相違",
        "Back": "difference,discrepancy,variation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 772
    },
    {
        "Front": "そういえば",
        "Back": "which reminds me ..",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "雑巾",
        "Back": "house-cloth,dust cloth",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 773
    },
    {
        "Front": "増減",
        "Back": "increase and decrease,fluctuation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 774
    },
    {
        "Front": "倉庫",
        "Back": "storehouse,warehouse,godown",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 775
    },
    {
        "Front": "相互",
        "Back": "mutual,reciprocal",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 776
    },
    {
        "Front": "創作",
        "Back": "production,literary creation,work",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 777
    },
    {
        "Front": "葬式",
        "Back": "funeral",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 778
    },
    {
        "Front": "そうして",
        "Back": "and,like that",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "造船",
        "Back": "shipbuilding",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 779
    },
    {
        "Front": "騒々しい",
        "Back": "noisy,boisterous",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 780
    },
    {
        "Front": "増大",
        "Back": "enlargement",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 781
    },
    {
        "Front": "そうっと",
        "Back": "",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "送別",
        "Back": "farewell,send-off",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 782
    },
    {
        "Front": "草履",
        "Back": "zoori (Japanese footwear),sandals",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 783
    },
    {
        "Front": "総理大臣",
        "Back": "Prime Minister",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 784
    },
    {
        "Front": "送料",
        "Back": "postage,carriage",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 785
    },
    {
        "Front": "属する",
        "Back": "to belong to,to come under,to be affiliated with,to be subject to",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 786
    },
    {
        "Front": "続々",
        "Back": "successively,one after another",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 787
    },
    {
        "Front": "速達",
        "Back": "express,special delivery",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 788
    },
    {
        "Front": "測定",
        "Back": "measurement",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 789
    },
    {
        "Front": "測量",
        "Back": "measurement,surveying",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 790
    },
    {
        "Front": "速力",
        "Back": "speed",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 791
    },
    {
        "Front": "素質",
        "Back": "character,qualities,genius",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 792
    },
    {
        "Front": "祖先",
        "Back": "ancestor",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 793
    },
    {
        "Front": "そそっかしい",
        "Back": "careless,thoughtless",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "卒直",
        "Back": "frankness,candour,openheartedness",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 794
    },
    {
        "Front": "具える",
        "Back": "to be furnished with",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 795
    },
    {
        "Front": "そのうえ",
        "Back": "in addition,furthermore",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "そのころ",
        "Back": "",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "そのため",
        "Back": "hence,for that reason",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "そのほか",
        "Back": "otherwise",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "蕎麦",
        "Back": "soba (buckwheat noodles)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 796
    },
    {
        "Front": "剃る",
        "Back": "to shave",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 797
    },
    {
        "Front": "それなのに",
        "Back": "",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "逸れる",
        "Back": "to stray (turn) from subject,to get lost,to go astray",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 798
    },
    {
        "Front": "揃う",
        "Back": "to become complete,to be equal,to be all present,to gather",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 799
    },
    {
        "Front": "揃える",
        "Back": "to put things in order,to arrange,to make uniform,to get something ready",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 800
    },
    {
        "Front": "算盤",
        "Back": "abacus",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 801
    },
    {
        "Front": "存じる",
        "Back": "(hum) to know",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 802
    },
    {
        "Front": "存ずる",
        "Back": "",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 803
    },
    {
        "Front": "損得",
        "Back": "loss and gain,advantage and disadvantage",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 804
    },
    {
        "Front": "田ぼ",
        "Back": "paddy field,farm",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 805
    },
    {
        "Front": "だいいち",
        "Back": "first,foremost,# 1",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "退院",
        "Back": "leaving hospital",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 807
    },
    {
        "Front": "大学院",
        "Back": "graduate school",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 808
    },
    {
        "Front": "大工",
        "Back": "carpenter",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 809
    },
    {
        "Front": "体系",
        "Back": "system,organization",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 810
    },
    {
        "Front": "太鼓",
        "Back": "drum,tambourine",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 811
    },
    {
        "Front": "対策",
        "Back": "counter-plan,counter-measure",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 812
    },
    {
        "Front": "大して",
        "Back": "(not so) much,(not) very",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 813
    },
    {
        "Front": "対照",
        "Back": "contrast,antithesis,comparison",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 814
    },
    {
        "Front": "大小",
        "Back": "size",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 815
    },
    {
        "Front": "体制",
        "Back": "order,system,structure,set-up,organization",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 816
    },
    {
        "Front": "体積",
        "Back": "capacity,volume",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 817
    },
    {
        "Front": "大層",
        "Back": "very much,exaggerated,very fine",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 818
    },
    {
        "Front": "体操",
        "Back": "gymnastics,physical exercises,calisthenics",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 819
    },
    {
        "Front": "大分",
        "Back": "considerably,greatly,a lot",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 820
    },
    {
        "Front": "大木",
        "Back": "large tree",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 821
    },
    {
        "Front": "題名",
        "Back": "title",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 822
    },
    {
        "Front": "代名詞",
        "Back": "pronoun",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 823
    },
    {
        "Front": "タイア",
        "Back": "tire,tyre",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ダイヤグラム",
        "Back": "diagram",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ダイヤモンド",
        "Back": "diamond",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ダイヤル",
        "Back": "dial",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "Ͼ立",
        "Back": "confrontation,opposition,antagonism",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 824
    },
    {
        "Front": "田植え",
        "Back": "rice planting",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 825
    },
    {
        "Front": "絶えず",
        "Back": "constantly",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 826
    },
    {
        "Front": "楕円",
        "Back": "ellipse",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 827
    },
    {
        "Front": "高める",
        "Back": "to raise,to lift,to boost",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 828
    },
    {
        "Front": "耕す",
        "Back": "to till,to plow,to cultivate",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 829
    },
    {
        "Front": "滝",
        "Back": "waterfall",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 830
    },
    {
        "Front": "炊く",
        "Back": "to boil,to cook",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 831
    },
    {
        "Front": "焚く",
        "Back": "to burn,to kindle,to build a fire",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 832
    },
    {
        "Front": "蓄える",
        "Back": "to store,to lay in stock",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 833
    },
    {
        "Front": "竹",
        "Back": "bamboo,middle (of a three-tier ranking system)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 834
    },
    {
        "Front": "助かる",
        "Back": "to be saved,to be rescued,to survive,to be helpful",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 835
    },
    {
        "Front": "只",
        "Back": "free of charge,mere,sole,only,usual,common",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 836
    },
    {
        "Front": "但し",
        "Back": "but,however,provided that",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 837
    },
    {
        "Front": "畳む",
        "Back": "to fold (clothes)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 838
    },
    {
        "Front": "立ち止まる",
        "Back": "to stop,to halt,to stand still",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 839
    },
    {
        "Front": "たちまち",
        "Back": "at once,in a moment,suddenly,all at once",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "建つ",
        "Back": "to erect,to be erected,to be built",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 840
    },
    {
        "Front": "発つ",
        "Back": "to depart (on a plane, train, etc.)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 841
    },
    {
        "Front": "脱線",
        "Back": "derailment,digression",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 842
    },
    {
        "Front": "妥当",
        "Back": "valid,proper,right,appropriate",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 843
    },
    {
        "Front": "例える",
        "Back": "to compare,to liken,to speak figuratively,to illustrate,to use a simile",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 844
    },
    {
        "Front": "頼もしい",
        "Back": "reliable,trustworthy,hopeful,promising",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 845
    },
    {
        "Front": "足袋",
        "Back": "tabi,Japanese socks (with split toe)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 846
    },
    {
        "Front": "ダブル",
        "Back": "double",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "だます",
        "Back": "to trick,to cheat,to deceive",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "溜まる",
        "Back": "to collect,to gather,to save",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 847
    },
    {
        "Front": "ダム",
        "Back": "dumb",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "溜息",
        "Back": "a sigh",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 848
    },
    {
        "Front": "ためらう",
        "Back": "to hesitate",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "溜める",
        "Back": "to amass,to accumulate",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 849
    },
    {
        "Front": "だらしない",
        "Back": "slovenly,loose,a slut",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "足る",
        "Back": "to be sufficient,to be enough",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 850
    },
    {
        "Front": "段階",
        "Back": "gradation,grade,stage",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 851
    },
    {
        "Front": "短期",
        "Back": "short term",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 852
    },
    {
        "Front": "炭鉱",
        "Back": "coal mine,coal pit",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 853
    },
    {
        "Front": "短所",
        "Back": "(1) defect,demerit,weak point,(2) disadvantage",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 854
    },
    {
        "Front": "たんす",
        "Back": "chest of drawers",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "淡水",
        "Back": "fresh water",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 855
    },
    {
        "Front": "断水",
        "Back": "water outage",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 856
    },
    {
        "Front": "単数",
        "Back": "singular (number)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 857
    },
    {
        "Front": "団地",
        "Back": "multi-unit apartments",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 858
    },
    {
        "Front": "断定",
        "Back": "conclusion,decision",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 859
    },
    {
        "Front": "短編",
        "Back": "short (e.g. story, film)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 860
    },
    {
        "Front": "誓う",
        "Back": "to swear,to vow,to take an oath,to pledge",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 861
    },
    {
        "Front": "地下水",
        "Back": "underground water",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 862
    },
    {
        "Front": "近々",
        "Back": "nearness,before long",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 863
    },
    {
        "Front": "近付ける",
        "Back": "to bring near,to put close,to let come near,to associate with",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 864
    },
    {
        "Front": "近寄る",
        "Back": "to approach,to draw near",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 865
    },
    {
        "Front": "力強い",
        "Back": "reassuring,emboldened",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 866
    },
    {
        "Front": "ちぎる",
        "Back": "to cut up fine,to pick (fruit)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "地質",
        "Back": "geological features",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 867
    },
    {
        "Front": "知人",
        "Back": "friend,acquaintance",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 868
    },
    {
        "Front": "地帯",
        "Back": "area,zone",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 869
    },
    {
        "Front": "縮む",
        "Back": "to shrink,to be contracted",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 870
    },
    {
        "Front": "縮める",
        "Back": "to shorten,to reduce,to boil down,to shrink",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 871
    },
    {
        "Front": "縮れる",
        "Back": "to be wavy,to be curled",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 872
    },
    {
        "Front": "チップ",
        "Back": "(1) gratuity,tip,(2) chip",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "地点",
        "Back": "site,point on a map",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 873
    },
    {
        "Front": "地名",
        "Back": "place name",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 874
    },
    {
        "Front": "茶色い",
        "Back": "",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 875
    },
    {
        "Front": "着々",
        "Back": "steadily",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 876
    },
    {
        "Front": "茶碗",
        "Back": "rice bowl,tea cup,teacup",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 877
    },
    {
        "Front": "中間",
        "Back": "middle,midway,interim",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 878
    },
    {
        "Front": "中旬",
        "Back": "second third of a month",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 879
    },
    {
        "Front": "抽象",
        "Back": "abstract",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 880
    },
    {
        "Front": "中世",
        "Back": "Middle Ages,mediaeval times",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 881
    },
    {
        "Front": "中性",
        "Back": "neuter gender,neutral (chem.),indifference,sterility",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 882
    },
    {
        "Front": "中途",
        "Back": "in the middle,half-way",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 883
    },
    {
        "Front": "中年",
        "Back": "middle-aged",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 884
    },
    {
        "Front": "超過",
        "Back": "excess,being more than",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 885
    },
    {
        "Front": "彫刻",
        "Back": "carving,engraving,sculpture",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 886
    },
    {
        "Front": "長所",
        "Back": "(1) strong point,merit,(2) advantage",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 887
    },
    {
        "Front": "長女",
        "Back": "eldest daughter",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 888
    },
    {
        "Front": "調整",
        "Back": "regulation,adjustment,tuning",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 889
    },
    {
        "Front": "調節",
        "Back": "regulation,adjustment,control",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 890
    },
    {
        "Front": "長短",
        "Back": "length,long and short,+-",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 891
    },
    {
        "Front": "頂点",
        "Back": "top,summit",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 892
    },
    {
        "Front": "長男",
        "Back": "eldest son",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 893
    },
    {
        "Front": "長方形",
        "Back": "rectangle,oblong",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 894
    },
    {
        "Front": "調味料",
        "Back": "condiment,seasoning",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 895
    },
    {
        "Front": "チョーク",
        "Back": "chock,chalk",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "直後",
        "Back": "immediately following",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 896
    },
    {
        "Front": "直線",
        "Back": "straight line",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 897
    },
    {
        "Front": "直前",
        "Back": "just before",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 898
    },
    {
        "Front": "直通",
        "Back": "direct communication",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 899
    },
    {
        "Front": "直流",
        "Back": "direct current",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 900
    },
    {
        "Front": "貯蔵",
        "Back": "storage,preservation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 901
    },
    {
        "Front": "直角",
        "Back": "right angle",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 902
    },
    {
        "Front": "直径",
        "Back": "diameter",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 903
    },
    {
        "Front": "散らかる",
        "Back": "to be in disorder,to lie scattered around",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 905
    },
    {
        "Front": "散らかす",
        "Back": "to scatter around,to leave untidy",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 904
    },
    {
        "Front": "散らす",
        "Back": "to scatter,to disperse,to distribute",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 906
    },
    {
        "Front": "塵紙",
        "Back": "tissue paper,toilet paper",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 907
    },
    {
        "Front": "散る",
        "Back": "to fall,to scatter (e.g. blossoms)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 908
    },
    {
        "Front": "追加",
        "Back": "addition,supplement,appendix",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 909
    },
    {
        "Front": "ついで",
        "Back": "opportunity,occasion",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "通貨",
        "Back": "currency",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 910
    },
    {
        "Front": "通勤",
        "Back": "commuting to work",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 911
    },
    {
        "Front": "通ずる",
        "Back": "",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 912
    },
    {
        "Front": "通知",
        "Back": "notice,notification",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 913
    },
    {
        "Front": "通訳",
        "Back": "interpretation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 915
    },
    {
        "Front": "通帳",
        "Back": "passbook",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 914
    },
    {
        "Front": "通用",
        "Back": "popular use,circulation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 916
    },
    {
        "Front": "通路",
        "Back": "passage,pathway",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 917
    },
    {
        "Front": "付合う",
        "Back": "to associate with,to keep company with,to get on with",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 918
    },
    {
        "Front": "突き当たり",
        "Back": "end (e.g. of street)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 919
    },
    {
        "Front": "突き当たる",
        "Back": "to run into,to collide with",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 920
    },
    {
        "Front": "月日",
        "Back": "time,years,days",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 921
    },
    {
        "Front": "点く",
        "Back": "to catch fire,(electricity) comes on",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 922
    },
    {
        "Front": "突く",
        "Back": "(1) to thrust,to strike,(2) to poke",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 923
    },
    {
        "Front": "次ぐ",
        "Back": "to rank next to,to come after",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 924
    },
    {
        "Front": "作る/造る",
        "Back": "to make,to create",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 925
    },
    {
        "Front": "着ける",
        "Back": "(1) to attach,to join,to add,to append",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 926
    },
    {
        "Front": "点ける",
        "Back": "to turn on,to switch on,to light up",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 927
    },
    {
        "Front": "浸ける",
        "Back": "to dip in,to soak",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 928
    },
    {
        "Front": "伝わる",
        "Back": "to be handed down,to be introduced,to be transmitted",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 929
    },
    {
        "Front": "突っ込む",
        "Back": "to plunge into,to go into deeply",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 930
    },
    {
        "Front": "務める",
        "Back": "(1) to serve,to fill a post,to serve under,to work (for)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 931
    },
    {
        "Front": "努める",
        "Back": "(1) to serve,to fill a post,to serve under,to work (for)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 932
    },
    {
        "Front": "綱",
        "Back": "rope",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 933
    },
    {
        "Front": "繋がり",
        "Back": "connection,link,relationship",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 934
    },
    {
        "Front": "繋がる",
        "Back": "to be tied together,to be connected to,to be related to",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 935
    },
    {
        "Front": "繋げる",
        "Back": "to connect",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 936
    },
    {
        "Front": "粒",
        "Back": "grain",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 937
    },
    {
        "Front": "潰す",
        "Back": "to smash,to waste",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 938
    },
    {
        "Front": "潰れる",
        "Back": "to be smashed,to go bankrupt",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 939
    },
    {
        "Front": "つまずく",
        "Back": "to stumble,to trip",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "詰まる",
        "Back": "to be blocked,to be packed",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 940
    },
    {
        "Front": "積む",
        "Back": "to pile up,to stack",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 941
    },
    {
        "Front": "爪",
        "Back": "fingernail or toenail,claw,talon,hoof",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 942
    },
    {
        "Front": "艶",
        "Back": "gloss,glaze",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 943
    },
    {
        "Front": "強気",
        "Back": "firm,strong",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 944
    },
    {
        "Front": "釣り合う",
        "Back": "to balance,to be in harmony,to suit",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 945
    },
    {
        "Front": "吊る",
        "Back": "to hang",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 946
    },
    {
        "Front": "吊す",
        "Back": "to hang",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 947
    },
    {
        "Front": "出合い",
        "Back": "an encounter",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 948
    },
    {
        "Front": "手洗い",
        "Back": "restroom,lavatory,hand-washing",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 949
    },
    {
        "Front": "定員",
        "Back": "fixed number of regular personnel,capacity (of boat, etc.)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 950
    },
    {
        "Front": "定価",
        "Back": "established price",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 951
    },
    {
        "Front": "低下",
        "Back": "fall,decline,lowering,deterioration",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 952
    },
    {
        "Front": "定期券",
        "Back": "commuter pass,season ticket",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 953
    },
    {
        "Front": "定休日",
        "Back": "regular holiday",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 954
    },
    {
        "Front": "停止",
        "Back": "suspension,interruption,stoppage,ban",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 955
    },
    {
        "Front": "停車",
        "Back": "stopping (e.g. train)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 956
    },
    {
        "Front": "停電",
        "Back": "failure of electricity",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 957
    },
    {
        "Front": "出入り",
        "Back": "in and out,coming and going,free association,income and expenditure,debits and credit",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 958
    },
    {
        "Front": "出入口",
        "Back": "exit and entrance",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 959
    },
    {
        "Front": "手入れ",
        "Back": "repairs,maintenance",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 960
    },
    {
        "Front": "テーマ",
        "Back": "(n) theme,project,topic (de: Thema)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "出掛ける",
        "Back": "to depart,to set out,to start,to be going out",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 961
    },
    {
        "Front": "出来上がり",
        "Back": "be finished,ready,made for,cut out",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 962
    },
    {
        "Front": "出来上がる",
        "Back": "(1) to be finished,to be ready,by definition,(2) to be very drunk",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 963
    },
    {
        "Front": "的確",
        "Back": "precise,accurate",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 964
    },
    {
        "Front": "適確",
        "Back": "precise,accurate",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 965
    },
    {
        "Front": "手首",
        "Back": "wrist",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 966
    },
    {
        "Front": "凸凹",
        "Back": "unevenness,roughness,ruggedness",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 967
    },
    {
        "Front": "手頃",
        "Back": "moderate,handy",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 968
    },
    {
        "Front": "でたらめ",
        "Back": "(1) irresponsible utterance,nonsense,nonsensical,(2) random",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "手帳",
        "Back": "notebook",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 969
    },
    {
        "Front": "鉄橋",
        "Back": "railway bridge,iron bridge",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 970
    },
    {
        "Front": "手続き",
        "Back": "procedure,(legal) process,formalities",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 971
    },
    {
        "Front": "鉄砲",
        "Back": "gun",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 972
    },
    {
        "Front": "テニスコート",
        "Back": "tennis court",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "手拭い",
        "Back": "(hand) towel",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 973
    },
    {
        "Front": "手前",
        "Back": "before,this side,we,you",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 974
    },
    {
        "Front": "出迎え",
        "Back": "meeting,reception",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 975
    },
    {
        "Front": "出迎える",
        "Back": "to meet,to greet",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 976
    },
    {
        "Front": "照らす",
        "Back": "to shine on,to illuminate",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 977
    },
    {
        "Front": "照る",
        "Back": "to shine",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 978
    },
    {
        "Front": "展開",
        "Back": "develop,expansion (opposite of compression)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 979
    },
    {
        "Front": "伝記",
        "Back": "biography,life story",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 980
    },
    {
        "Front": "電球",
        "Back": "light bulb",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 981
    },
    {
        "Front": "点数",
        "Back": "marks,points,score,runs",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 982
    },
    {
        "Front": "伝染",
        "Back": "contagion",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 983
    },
    {
        "Front": "電池",
        "Back": "battery",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 984
    },
    {
        "Front": "点々",
        "Back": "here and there,little by little",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 985
    },
    {
        "Front": "転々",
        "Back": "",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 986
    },
    {
        "Front": "電柱",
        "Back": "telephone pole,telegraph pole,lightpole",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 987
    },
    {
        "Front": "天皇",
        "Back": "Emperor of Japan",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 988
    },
    {
        "Front": "電波",
        "Back": "electro-magnetic wave",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 989
    },
    {
        "Front": "テンポ",
        "Back": "tempo",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "電流",
        "Back": "electric current",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 990
    },
    {
        "Front": "電力",
        "Back": "electric power",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 991
    },
    {
        "Front": "問い合わせ",
        "Back": "enquiry,ENQ",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 992
    },
    {
        "Front": "銅",
        "Back": "copper",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 993
    },
    {
        "Front": "統一",
        "Back": "unity,consolidation,uniformity",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 994
    },
    {
        "Front": "同格",
        "Back": "the same rank,equality,apposition",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 995
    },
    {
        "Front": "峠",
        "Back": "ridge,(mountain) pass,difficult part",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 996
    },
    {
        "Front": "統計",
        "Back": "scattering,a scatter,dispersion",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 997
    },
    {
        "Front": "動作",
        "Back": "action,movements,motions,bearing,behaviour,manners",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 998
    },
    {
        "Front": "東西",
        "Back": "East and West,whole country",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 999
    },
    {
        "Front": "当日",
        "Back": "appointed day,very day",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1000
    },
    {
        "Front": "投書",
        "Back": "letter to the editor,letter from a reader,contribution",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1001
    },
    {
        "Front": "登場",
        "Back": "entry (on stage)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1002
    },
    {
        "Front": "どうせ",
        "Back": "anyhow,in any case,at any rate",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "どうぞよろしく",
        "Back": "pleased to meet you",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "灯台",
        "Back": "lighthouse",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1003
    },
    {
        "Front": "盗難",
        "Back": "theft,robbery",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1004
    },
    {
        "Front": "当番",
        "Back": "being on duty",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1005
    },
    {
        "Front": "等分",
        "Back": "division into equal parts",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1006
    },
    {
        "Front": "透明",
        "Back": "transparency,cleanness",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1007
    },
    {
        "Front": "灯油",
        "Back": "lamp oil,kerosene",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1008
    },
    {
        "Front": "東洋",
        "Back": "Orient",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1009
    },
    {
        "Front": "童話",
        "Back": "fairy tale",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1010
    },
    {
        "Front": "通り掛かる",
        "Back": "to happen to pass by",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1011
    },
    {
        "Front": "溶かす",
        "Back": "to melt,to dissolve",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1012
    },
    {
        "Front": "尖る",
        "Back": "to taper to a point,to become sharp,to be sour,to look displeased",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1013
    },
    {
        "Front": "どきどき",
        "Back": "throb,beat (fast)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "溶く",
        "Back": "to dissolve (paint)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1014
    },
    {
        "Front": "退く",
        "Back": "(1) to retreat,to recede,to withdraw",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1015
    },
    {
        "Front": "特殊",
        "Back": "special,unique",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1016
    },
    {
        "Front": "特色",
        "Back": "characteristic,feature",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1017
    },
    {
        "Front": "特長",
        "Back": "forte,merit",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1018
    },
    {
        "Front": "特定",
        "Back": "specific,special,particular",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1019
    },
    {
        "Front": "特売",
        "Back": "special sale",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1020
    },
    {
        "Front": "溶け込む",
        "Back": "to melt into",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1021
    },
    {
        "Front": "溶ける",
        "Back": "to melt,to thaw,to fuse,to dissolve",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1022
    },
    {
        "Front": "退ける",
        "Back": "to remove,to take away,to dislodge,to put something out of the way",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1023
    },
    {
        "Front": "床の間",
        "Back": "alcove",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1024
    },
    {
        "Front": "床屋",
        "Back": "barber",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1025
    },
    {
        "Front": "所々",
        "Back": "here and there,some parts (of something)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1026
    },
    {
        "Front": "都心",
        "Back": "heart (of city)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1027
    },
    {
        "Front": "戸棚",
        "Back": "cupboard,locker,closet,wardrobe",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1028
    },
    {
        "Front": "とっくに",
        "Back": "long ago,already,a long time ago",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "どっと",
        "Back": "suddenly",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "整う",
        "Back": "to be prepared,to be in order,to be put in order,to be arranged",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1029
    },
    {
        "Front": "留まる",
        "Back": "(1) to be fixed,(2) to abide,to stay (in the one place)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1030
    },
    {
        "Front": "どなる",
        "Back": "to shout,to yell",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "飛び込む",
        "Back": "to jump in,to leap in,to plunge into,to dive",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1031
    },
    {
        "Front": "跳ぶ",
        "Back": "to jump,to fly,to leap",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1032
    },
    {
        "Front": "泊める",
        "Back": "to give shelter to,to lodge",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1033
    },
    {
        "Front": "ともかく",
        "Back": "anyhow,anyway,somehow or other,generally speaking,in any case",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "捕える",
        "Back": "to seize,to grasp,to capture,to arrest",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1034
    },
    {
        "Front": "取り入れる",
        "Back": "to harvest,to take in,to adopt",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1035
    },
    {
        "Front": "取り消す",
        "Back": "to cancel",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1036
    },
    {
        "Front": "取り出す",
        "Back": "to take out,to produce,to pick out",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1037
    },
    {
        "Front": "採る",
        "Back": "(1) to adopt (measure, proposal),(2) to pick (fruit)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1038
    },
    {
        "Front": "捕る",
        "Back": "to take,to catch (fish),to capture",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1039
    },
    {
        "Front": "トレーニング",
        "Back": "training",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "丼",
        "Back": "porcelain bowl,bowl of rice with food on top",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1040
    },
    {
        "Front": "内科",
        "Back": "internist clinic,internal medicine",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1041
    },
    {
        "Front": "内線",
        "Back": "phone extension,indoor wiring,inner line",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1042
    },
    {
        "Front": "ナイロン",
        "Back": "nylon",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "治す",
        "Back": "to cure,to heal,to fix,to correct,to repair",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1043
    },
    {
        "Front": "永い",
        "Back": "long,lengthy",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1044
    },
    {
        "Front": "仲直り",
        "Back": "reconciliation,make peace with",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1045
    },
    {
        "Front": "長引く",
        "Back": "to be prolonged,to drag on",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1046
    },
    {
        "Front": "中身",
        "Back": "contents,interior,substance,filling,(sword) blade",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1047
    },
    {
        "Front": "中味",
        "Back": "contents,interior,substance,filling,(sword) blade",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1048
    },
    {
        "Front": "中指",
        "Back": "middle finger",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1049
    },
    {
        "Front": "仲良し",
        "Back": "intimate friend,bosom buddy,chum",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1050
    },
    {
        "Front": "慰める",
        "Back": "to comfort,to console",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1051
    },
    {
        "Front": "亡くす",
        "Back": "to lose someone, wife, child, etc",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1052
    },
    {
        "Front": "なぐる",
        "Back": "to strike,to hit",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "為す",
        "Back": "to accomplish,to do",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1053
    },
    {
        "Front": "謎謎",
        "Back": "riddle,puzzle,enigma",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1054
    },
    {
        "Front": "傾らか",
        "Back": "",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1055
    },
    {
        "Front": "懐かしい",
        "Back": "dear,desired,missed",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1056
    },
    {
        "Front": "撫でる",
        "Back": "to brush gently,to stroke",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1057
    },
    {
        "Front": "斜め",
        "Back": "obliqueness",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1058
    },
    {
        "Front": "なにしろ",
        "Back": "at any rate,anyhow,anyway,in any case",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "何々",
        "Back": "such and such,What?",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1059
    },
    {
        "Front": "何分",
        "Back": "what minute?,how many minutes?",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1060
    },
    {
        "Front": "生意気",
        "Back": "impertinent,saucy,cheeky,conceit,audacious,brazen",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1061
    },
    {
        "Front": "並木",
        "Back": "roadside tree,row of trees",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1062
    },
    {
        "Front": "倣う",
        "Back": "to imitate,to follow,to emulate",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1063
    },
    {
        "Front": "鳴らす",
        "Back": "to ring,to sound,to chime,to beat,to snort (nose)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1064
    },
    {
        "Front": "生る",
        "Back": "to bear fruit",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1065
    },
    {
        "Front": "馴れる",
        "Back": "to become domesticated,to become tame",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1066
    },
    {
        "Front": "南極",
        "Back": "south pole,Antarctic",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1067
    },
    {
        "Front": "なんとなく",
        "Back": "somehow or other,for some reason or another",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "なんとも",
        "Back": "nothing (with neg. verb),quite,not a bit",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ナンバー",
        "Back": "number",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "南米",
        "Back": "South America",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1068
    },
    {
        "Front": "南北",
        "Back": "south and north",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1069
    },
    {
        "Front": "煮える",
        "Back": "to boil,to cook,to be cooked",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1070
    },
    {
        "Front": "匂う",
        "Back": "to be fragrant,to smell,to stink",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1071
    },
    {
        "Front": "逃がす",
        "Back": "to let loose,to set free,to let escape",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1072
    },
    {
        "Front": "憎い",
        "Back": "hateful,abominable,poor-looking,detestable",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1073
    },
    {
        "Front": "憎む",
        "Back": "to hate,to detest",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1074
    },
    {
        "Front": "憎らしい",
        "Back": "odious,hateful",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1075
    },
    {
        "Front": "にこにこ",
        "Back": "",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "濁る",
        "Back": "to become muddy,to get impure",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1076
    },
    {
        "Front": "虹",
        "Back": "rainbow",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1077
    },
    {
        "Front": "日時",
        "Back": "date and time",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1078
    },
    {
        "Front": "日用品",
        "Back": "daily necessities",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1079
    },
    {
        "Front": "日課",
        "Back": "daily lesson,daily work,daily routine",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1080
    },
    {
        "Front": "日程",
        "Back": "agenda",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1081
    },
    {
        "Front": "鈍い",
        "Back": "dull (e.g. a knife),thickheaded,slow (opposite of fast),stupid",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1082
    },
    {
        "Front": "入社",
        "Back": "entry to a company",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1083
    },
    {
        "Front": "女房",
        "Back": "wife",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1084
    },
    {
        "Front": "睨む",
        "Back": "to glare at,to scowl at,to keep an eye on",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1085
    },
    {
        "Front": "煮る",
        "Back": "to boil,to cook",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1086
    },
    {
        "Front": "俄",
        "Back": "sudden,abrupt,unexpected,improvised,offhand",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1087
    },
    {
        "Front": "縫う",
        "Back": "to sew",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1088
    },
    {
        "Front": "濡らす",
        "Back": "to wet,to soak,to dip",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1089
    },
    {
        "Front": "ねじ",
        "Back": "(a) screw",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "捩る",
        "Back": "to twist",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1091
    },
    {
        "Front": "ネックレス",
        "Back": "necklace",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "熱する",
        "Back": "to heat",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1090
    },
    {
        "Front": "寝間着",
        "Back": "sleep-wear,nightclothes,pyjamas,nightgown,nightdress",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1092
    },
    {
        "Front": "寝巻",
        "Back": "sleep-wear,nightclothes,pyjamas,nightgown,nightdress",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1093
    },
    {
        "Front": "狙い",
        "Back": "aim",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1095
    },
    {
        "Front": "狙う",
        "Back": "to aim at",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1094
    },
    {
        "Front": "年度",
        "Back": "year,fiscal year,school year,term",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1096
    },
    {
        "Front": "農産物",
        "Back": "agricultural produce",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1097
    },
    {
        "Front": "農村",
        "Back": "agricultural community,farm village,rural",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1098
    },
    {
        "Front": "濃度",
        "Back": "concentration,brightness",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1099
    },
    {
        "Front": "農薬",
        "Back": "agricultural chemicals",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1100
    },
    {
        "Front": "能率",
        "Back": "efficiency",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1101
    },
    {
        "Front": "のこぎり",
        "Back": "saw",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "残らず",
        "Back": "all,entirely,completely,without exception",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1102
    },
    {
        "Front": "載せる",
        "Back": "to place on (something),to take on board,to give a ride",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1103
    },
    {
        "Front": "覗く",
        "Back": "to peep in,to look in,to peek in,to stick out",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1104
    },
    {
        "Front": "延ばす",
        "Back": "to lengthen,to stretch,to reach out,to grow (beard)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1105
    },
    {
        "Front": "延びる",
        "Back": "to be prolonged",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1106
    },
    {
        "Front": "上り",
        "Back": "up-train (going to Tokyo),ascent",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1107
    },
    {
        "Front": "上る",
        "Back": "to ascend,to go up,to climb",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1108
    },
    {
        "Front": "糊",
        "Back": "paste,starch",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1109
    },
    {
        "Front": "乗換",
        "Back": "(n) transfer (trains, buses, etc.)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1110
    },
    {
        "Front": "載る",
        "Back": "to appear (in print),to be recorded",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1111
    },
    {
        "Front": "のろのろ",
        "Back": "slowly,sluggishly",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "呑気",
        "Back": "carefree,optimistic,careless,reckless,heedless",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1112
    },
    {
        "Front": "灰色",
        "Back": "grey,gray,ashen",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1113
    },
    {
        "Front": "俳句",
        "Back": "haiku poetry",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1114
    },
    {
        "Front": "拝見",
        "Back": "(hum) (pol) seeing,look at",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1115
    },
    {
        "Front": "売店",
        "Back": "shop,stand",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1116
    },
    {
        "Front": "バイバイ",
        "Back": "",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "売買",
        "Back": "trade,buying and selling",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1117
    },
    {
        "Front": "這う",
        "Back": "to creep,to crawl",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1118
    },
    {
        "Front": "生える",
        "Back": "(1) to grow,to spring up,(2) to cut (teeth)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1119
    },
    {
        "Front": "剥す",
        "Back": "(v5s) to tear off,to peel off,to rip off",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1120
    },
    {
        "Front": "ばからしい",
        "Back": "absurd",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "秤",
        "Back": "scales,weighing machine",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1121
    },
    {
        "Front": "量る",
        "Back": "to measure,to weigh,to survey",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1122
    },
    {
        "Front": "測る",
        "Back": "to measure,to weigh,to survey",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1123
    },
    {
        "Front": "吐き気",
        "Back": "nausea,sickness in the stomach",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1124
    },
    {
        "Front": "はきはき",
        "Back": "lucidly",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "掃く",
        "Back": "to sweep,to brush,to gather up",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1125
    },
    {
        "Front": "歯車",
        "Back": "gear,cog-wheel",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1126
    },
    {
        "Front": "バケツ",
        "Back": "bucket,pail",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "挟まる",
        "Back": "to get between,to be caught in",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1127
    },
    {
        "Front": "挟む",
        "Back": "to interpose,to hold between,to insert",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1128
    },
    {
        "Front": "箸",
        "Back": "chopsticks",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1129
    },
    {
        "Front": "梯子",
        "Back": "ladder,stairs",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1130
    },
    {
        "Front": "始めに",
        "Back": "to begin with,first of all",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1131
    },
    {
        "Front": "初めに",
        "Back": "",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1132
    },
    {
        "Front": "はじめまして",
        "Back": "How do you do?,I am glad to meet you",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "斜",
        "Back": "",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1133
    },
    {
        "Front": "外れる",
        "Back": "to be disconnected,to get out of place,to be off,to be out (e.g. of gear)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1134
    },
    {
        "Front": "パターン",
        "Back": "pattern",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "肌着",
        "Back": "underwear",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1135
    },
    {
        "Front": "果して",
        "Back": "as was expected,really",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1136
    },
    {
        "Front": "鉢",
        "Back": "a bowl,a pot",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1137
    },
    {
        "Front": "×",
        "Back": "",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "発揮",
        "Back": "exhibition,demonstration,utilization,display",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1139
    },
    {
        "Front": "バック",
        "Back": "back",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "発射",
        "Back": "firing,shooting,discharge,catapult",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1140
    },
    {
        "Front": "発想",
        "Back": "expression (music),conceptualization",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1141
    },
    {
        "Front": "発電",
        "Back": "generation (e.g. power)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1142
    },
    {
        "Front": "発売",
        "Back": "sale",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1143
    },
    {
        "Front": "派手",
        "Back": "showy,loud,gay,flashy,gaudy",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1144
    },
    {
        "Front": "話合い",
        "Back": "discussion,conference",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1145
    },
    {
        "Front": "話し掛ける",
        "Back": "to accost a person,to talk (to someone)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1146
    },
    {
        "Front": "話中",
        "Back": "while talking,the line is busy",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1147
    },
    {
        "Front": "甚だしい",
        "Back": "extreme,excessive,terrible",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1148
    },
    {
        "Front": "花火",
        "Back": "fireworks",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1149
    },
    {
        "Front": "花嫁",
        "Back": "bride",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1150
    },
    {
        "Front": "放れる",
        "Back": "to leave,to get free,to cut oneself off",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1151
    },
    {
        "Front": "羽根",
        "Back": "shuttlecock",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1152
    },
    {
        "Front": "ばね",
        "Back": "spring (e.g. coil, leaf)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "跳ねる",
        "Back": "to jump,to leap",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1153
    },
    {
        "Front": "破片",
        "Back": "fragment,splinter,broken piece",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1154
    },
    {
        "Front": "歯磨き",
        "Back": "dentifrice,toothpaste",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1155
    },
    {
        "Front": "はめる",
        "Back": "(col) to get in,to insert,to put on,to make love",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "早口",
        "Back": "fast-talking",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1156
    },
    {
        "Front": "流行る",
        "Back": "to flourish,to thrive,to be popular,to come into fashion",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1157
    },
    {
        "Front": "払い込む",
        "Back": "to deposit,to pay in",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1158
    },
    {
        "Front": "払い戻す",
        "Back": "to repay,to pay back",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1159
    },
    {
        "Front": "バランス",
        "Back": "balance",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "針金",
        "Back": "wire",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1160
    },
    {
        "Front": "張り切る",
        "Back": "to be in high spirits,to be full of vigor",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1161
    },
    {
        "Front": "反映",
        "Back": "reflection,influence",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1162
    },
    {
        "Front": "半径",
        "Back": "radius",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1163
    },
    {
        "Front": "判子",
        "Back": "seal (used for signature)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1164
    },
    {
        "Front": "万歳",
        "Back": "hurrah, cheers",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1165
    },
    {
        "Front": "判事",
        "Back": "judge,judiciary",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1166
    },
    {
        "Front": "反省",
        "Back": "reflection,reconsideration,introspection,meditation,contemplation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1167
    },
    {
        "Front": "番地",
        "Back": "house number,address",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1168
    },
    {
        "Front": "パンツ",
        "Back": "underpants",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "バンド",
        "Back": "band",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "半島",
        "Back": "peninsula",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1169
    },
    {
        "Front": "ハンドル",
        "Back": "handle,steering wheel",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "日当たり",
        "Back": "exposure to the sun,sunny place",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1170
    },
    {
        "Front": "日帰り",
        "Back": "day trip",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1171
    },
    {
        "Front": "比較的",
        "Back": "comparatively,relatively",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1172
    },
    {
        "Front": "日陰",
        "Back": "shadow",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1173
    },
    {
        "Front": "ぴかぴか",
        "Back": "glitter,sparkle",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "引受る",
        "Back": "to undertake,to take up,to take over",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1174
    },
    {
        "Front": "引返す",
        "Back": "to repeat,to send back,to bring back",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1175
    },
    {
        "Front": "引算",
        "Back": "subtraction",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1176
    },
    {
        "Front": "引出す",
        "Back": "to pull out,to take out,to draw out,to withdraw",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1177
    },
    {
        "Front": "引き止める",
        "Back": "to detain,to check,to restrain",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1178
    },
    {
        "Front": "卑怯",
        "Back": "cowardice,meanness,unfairness",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1179
    },
    {
        "Front": "引分け",
        "Back": "a draw (in competition),tie game",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1180
    },
    {
        "Front": "髭",
        "Back": "moustache,beard,whiskers",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1181
    },
    {
        "Front": "陽射",
        "Back": "sunlight,rays of the sun",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1182
    },
    {
        "Front": "肘",
        "Back": "elbow",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1183
    },
    {
        "Front": "ピストル",
        "Back": "pistol",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ビタミン",
        "Back": "vitamin",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ぴたり",
        "Back": "",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "引っ掛かる",
        "Back": "to be caught in,to be stuck in,to be cheated",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1184
    },
    {
        "Front": "筆記",
        "Back": "(taking) notes,copying",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1185
    },
    {
        "Front": "引っ繰り返す",
        "Back": "to turn over,to overturn,to knock over,to upset,to turn inside out",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1186
    },
    {
        "Front": "引っ繰り返る",
        "Back": "to be overturned,to be upset,to topple over,to be reversed",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1187
    },
    {
        "Front": "引越し",
        "Back": "moving (dwelling etc.),changing residence",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1188
    },
    {
        "Front": "引っ込む",
        "Back": "to draw back,to sink,to cave in",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1189
    },
    {
        "Front": "筆者",
        "Back": "writer,author",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1190
    },
    {
        "Front": "必需品",
        "Back": "necessities,necessary article,requisite,essential",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1191
    },
    {
        "Front": "人差指",
        "Back": "index finger",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1192
    },
    {
        "Front": "一通り",
        "Back": "ordinary,usual,in general,briefly",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1193
    },
    {
        "Front": "人通り",
        "Back": "pedestrian traffic",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1194
    },
    {
        "Front": "ひとまず",
        "Back": "for the present,once,in outline",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "瞳",
        "Back": "pupil (of eye)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1195
    },
    {
        "Front": "一休み",
        "Back": "a rest",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1196
    },
    {
        "Front": "独り言",
        "Back": "a soliloquy,a monologue,speaking to oneself",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1197
    },
    {
        "Front": "ひとりでに",
        "Back": "by itself,automatically,naturally",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ビニール",
        "Back": "vinyl",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "皮肉",
        "Back": "cynicism,sarcasm",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1198
    },
    {
        "Front": "日日",
        "Back": "every day,daily,day after day",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1199
    },
    {
        "Front": "捻る",
        "Back": "to turn (a switch) on or off,to twist,to puzzle over",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1200
    },
    {
        "Front": "日の入り",
        "Back": "sunset",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1201
    },
    {
        "Front": "日の出",
        "Back": "sunrise",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1202
    },
    {
        "Front": "響き",
        "Back": "echo,sound,reverberation,noise",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1203
    },
    {
        "Front": "響く",
        "Back": "to resound",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1204
    },
    {
        "Front": "皮膚",
        "Back": "skin",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1205
    },
    {
        "Front": "冷やす",
        "Back": "to cool,to refrigerate",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1206
    },
    {
        "Front": "ひゃっかじてん",
        "Back": "encyclopedia",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "美容",
        "Back": "beauty of figure or form",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1207
    },
    {
        "Front": "表紙",
        "Back": "front cover,binding",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1208
    },
    {
        "Front": "標識",
        "Back": "sign,mark",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1209
    },
    {
        "Front": "標準",
        "Back": "standard,level",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1210
    },
    {
        "Front": "標本",
        "Back": "example,specimen",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1211
    },
    {
        "Front": "評論",
        "Back": "criticism,critique",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1212
    },
    {
        "Front": "平仮名",
        "Back": "hiragana,47 syllables,the cursive syllabary",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1213
    },
    {
        "Front": "ビルディング",
        "Back": "building",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "昼寝",
        "Back": "nap (at home),siesta",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1214
    },
    {
        "Front": "広げる",
        "Back": "to spread,to extend,to expand,to enlarge",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1215
    },
    {
        "Front": "広さ",
        "Back": "extent",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1216
    },
    {
        "Front": "広場",
        "Back": "plaza",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1217
    },
    {
        "Front": "広々",
        "Back": "extensive,spacious",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1218
    },
    {
        "Front": "広める",
        "Back": "to broaden,to propagate",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1219
    },
    {
        "Front": "ピンク",
        "Back": "pink",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "便箋",
        "Back": "writing paper,stationery",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1220
    },
    {
        "Front": "瓶詰",
        "Back": "bottling,bottled",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1221
    },
    {
        "Front": "ファスナー",
        "Back": "fastener,zipper",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "風船",
        "Back": "balloon",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1222
    },
    {
        "Front": "不運",
        "Back": "unlucky,misfortune,bad luck,fate",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1223
    },
    {
        "Front": "殖える",
        "Back": "to increase,to multiply",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1224
    },
    {
        "Front": "深まる",
        "Back": "to deepen,to heighten,to intensify",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1225
    },
    {
        "Front": "不規則",
        "Back": "irregularity,unsteadiness,disorderly",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1226
    },
    {
        "Front": "普及",
        "Back": "diffusion,spread",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1227
    },
    {
        "Front": "付近",
        "Back": "neighbourhood,vicinity,environs",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1228
    },
    {
        "Front": "拭く",
        "Back": "to wipe,to dry",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1229
    },
    {
        "Front": "副詞",
        "Back": "adverb",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1230
    },
    {
        "Front": "複写",
        "Back": "copy,duplicate",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1231
    },
    {
        "Front": "複数",
        "Back": "plural,multiple",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1232
    },
    {
        "Front": "含める",
        "Back": "to include,to instruct,to make one understand",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1233
    },
    {
        "Front": "膨らます",
        "Back": "to swell,to expand,to inflate,to bulge",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1234
    },
    {
        "Front": "膨らむ",
        "Back": "to expand,to swell (out),to get big,to become inflated",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1235
    },
    {
        "Front": "不潔",
        "Back": "unclean,dirty,filthy,impure",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1236
    },
    {
        "Front": "更ける",
        "Back": "to get late,to advance,to wear on",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1237
    },
    {
        "Front": "符号",
        "Back": "sign,mark,symbol",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1238
    },
    {
        "Front": "夫妻",
        "Back": "man and wife,married couple",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1239
    },
    {
        "Front": "塞がる",
        "Back": "to be plugged up,to be shut up",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1240
    },
    {
        "Front": "塞ぐ",
        "Back": "to stop up,to close up,to block (up)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1241
    },
    {
        "Front": "ふざける",
        "Back": "to romp,to gambol,to frolic,to joke",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "無沙汰",
        "Back": "neglecting to stay in contact",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1242
    },
    {
        "Front": "武士",
        "Back": "warrior,samurai",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1243
    },
    {
        "Front": "部首",
        "Back": "radical (of a kanji character)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1244
    },
    {
        "Front": "襖",
        "Back": "sliding screen",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1245
    },
    {
        "Front": "附属",
        "Back": "attached,belonging,affiliated",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1246
    },
    {
        "Front": "蓋",
        "Back": "cover,lid,cap",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1247
    },
    {
        "Front": "不通",
        "Back": "suspension,interruption,stoppage,tie-up,cessation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1248
    },
    {
        "Front": "ぶつかる",
        "Back": "to strike,to collide with",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ぶつける",
        "Back": "to knock,to run into,to nail on,to strike hard,to hit and attack",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "物騒",
        "Back": "dangerous,disturbed,insecure",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1249
    },
    {
        "Front": "ぶつぶつ",
        "Back": "grumbling,complaining in a small voice",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "船便",
        "Back": "surface mail (ship)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1250
    },
    {
        "Front": "部品",
        "Back": "parts,accessories",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1251
    },
    {
        "Front": "吹雪",
        "Back": "snow storm",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1252
    },
    {
        "Front": "父母",
        "Back": "father and mother,parents",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1253
    },
    {
        "Front": "踏切",
        "Back": "railway crossing,level crossing,starting line,scratch,crossover",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1254
    },
    {
        "Front": "麓",
        "Back": "the foot,the bottom,the base (of a mountain)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1255
    },
    {
        "Front": "増やす",
        "Back": "to increase,to add to,to augment",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1256
    },
    {
        "Front": "殖やす",
        "Back": "to increase,to add to,to augment",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1257
    },
    {
        "Front": "フライパン",
        "Back": "fry pan,frying pan",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ブラウス",
        "Back": "blouse",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ぶらさげる",
        "Back": "to hang,to suspend,to dangle,to swing",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ブラシ",
        "Back": "brushy,brush",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "プラスチック",
        "Back": "plastic",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "プラットホーム",
        "Back": "platform",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "フリー",
        "Back": "free",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "振り仮名",
        "Back": ",pronunciation key",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1258
    },
    {
        "Front": "プリント",
        "Back": "print,handout",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "振舞う",
        "Back": "to behave,to conduct oneself,to entertain (vt)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1259
    },
    {
        "Front": "ブローチ",
        "Back": "brooch",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "プログラム",
        "Back": "program",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "風呂敷",
        "Back": "wrapping cloth,cloth wrapper",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1260
    },
    {
        "Front": "ふわふわ",
        "Back": "light,soft",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "噴火",
        "Back": "eruption",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1261
    },
    {
        "Front": "分解",
        "Back": "analysis,disassembly",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1262
    },
    {
        "Front": "文芸",
        "Back": "literature,art and literature,belles-lettres",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1263
    },
    {
        "Front": "文献",
        "Back": "literature,books (reference)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1264
    },
    {
        "Front": "噴水",
        "Back": "water fountain",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1265
    },
    {
        "Front": "分数",
        "Back": "fraction (in math)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1266
    },
    {
        "Front": "文体",
        "Back": "literary style",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1267
    },
    {
        "Front": "分布",
        "Back": "distribution",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1268
    },
    {
        "Front": "文房具",
        "Back": "stationery",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1269
    },
    {
        "Front": "文脈",
        "Back": "context",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1270
    },
    {
        "Front": "分量",
        "Back": "amount,quantity",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1271
    },
    {
        "Front": "分類",
        "Back": "classification",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1272
    },
    {
        "Front": "閉会",
        "Back": "closure",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1273
    },
    {
        "Front": "平気",
        "Back": "coolness,calmness,composure,unconcern",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1274
    },
    {
        "Front": "並行",
        "Back": "(going) side by side,concurrent,abreast,at the same time",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1275
    },
    {
        "Front": "平日",
        "Back": "weekday,ordinary days",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1276
    },
    {
        "Front": "兵隊",
        "Back": "soldier,sailor",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1277
    },
    {
        "Front": "平凡",
        "Back": "common,commonplace,ordinary,mediocre",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1278
    },
    {
        "Front": "平野",
        "Back": "plain,open field",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1279
    },
    {
        "Front": "凹む",
        "Back": "to be dented,to be indented,to yield to,to give,to sink,to collapse,to cave in,to be snubbed",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1280
    },
    {
        "Front": "へそ",
        "Back": "navel,belly-button",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "隔てる",
        "Back": "to be shut out",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1281
    },
    {
        "Front": "別荘",
        "Back": "holiday house,villa",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1282
    },
    {
        "Front": "別々",
        "Back": "separately,individually",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1283
    },
    {
        "Front": "ベテラン",
        "Back": "veteran",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ヘリコプター",
        "Back": "helicopter",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "へる",
        "Back": "to decrease (in size or number),to diminish,to abate",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ぺん",
        "Back": "pen",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "編集",
        "Back": "editing,compilation,editorial (e.g. committee)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1284
    },
    {
        "Front": "便所",
        "Back": "toilet,lavatory,rest room,latrine,comfort station",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1285
    },
    {
        "Front": "ペンチ",
        "Back": "(abbr) pliers (lit: pinchers)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "望遠鏡",
        "Back": "telescope",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1286
    },
    {
        "Front": "方角",
        "Back": "direction,way,compass point",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1287
    },
    {
        "Front": "箒",
        "Back": "(n) broom",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1288
    },
    {
        "Front": "方言",
        "Back": "dialect",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1289
    },
    {
        "Front": "坊さん",
        "Back": "Buddhist priest,monk",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1290
    },
    {
        "Front": "防止",
        "Back": "prevention,check",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1291
    },
    {
        "Front": "方針",
        "Back": "objective,plan,policy",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1292
    },
    {
        "Front": "包装",
        "Back": "packing,wrapping",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1293
    },
    {
        "Front": "法則",
        "Back": "law,rule",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1294
    },
    {
        "Front": "包帯",
        "Back": "bandage,dressing",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1295
    },
    {
        "Front": "膨大",
        "Back": "huge,bulky,enormous,extensive,swelling,expansion",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1296
    },
    {
        "Front": "庖丁",
        "Back": "kitchen knife,carving knife",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1297
    },
    {
        "Front": "方程式",
        "Back": "equation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1298
    },
    {
        "Front": "防犯",
        "Back": "prevention of crime",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1299
    },
    {
        "Front": "方面",
        "Back": "direction,district,field (e.g., of study)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1300
    },
    {
        "Front": "坊や",
        "Back": "boy",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1301
    },
    {
        "Front": "放る",
        "Back": "to let go",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1302
    },
    {
        "Front": "ボーナス",
        "Back": "bonus",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "朗らか",
        "Back": "brightness,cheerfulness,melodious",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1303
    },
    {
        "Front": "牧場",
        "Back": "(1) farm (livestock),(2) pasture land,meadow,grazing land",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1304
    },
    {
        "Front": "牧畜",
        "Back": "stock-farming",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1305
    },
    {
        "Front": "保健",
        "Back": "health preservation,hygiene,sanitation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1306
    },
    {
        "Front": "募集",
        "Back": "recruiting,taking applications",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1307
    },
    {
        "Front": "干す",
        "Back": "to air,to dry,to desiccate,to drain (off),to drink up",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1308
    },
    {
        "Front": "ポスター",
        "Back": "poster",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "北極",
        "Back": "North Pole",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1309
    },
    {
        "Front": "坊っちゃん",
        "Back": "son (of others)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1310
    },
    {
        "Front": "ほどく",
        "Back": "to unfasten",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "堀",
        "Back": "moat,canal",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1311
    },
    {
        "Front": "掘る",
        "Back": "to dig,to excavate",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1312
    },
    {
        "Front": "彫る",
        "Back": "to carve,to engrave,to sculpture,to chisel",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1313
    },
    {
        "Front": "ぼろ",
        "Back": "rag,scrap,tattered clothes,fault (esp. in a pretense)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "盆",
        "Back": "Lantern Festival,Festival of the Dead,tray",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1314
    },
    {
        "Front": "盆地",
        "Back": "basin (e.g. between mountains)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1315
    },
    {
        "Front": "本部",
        "Back": "headquarters",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1316
    },
    {
        "Front": "本来",
        "Back": "essentially,naturally,by nature",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1317
    },
    {
        "Front": "まあまあ",
        "Back": "so-so",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "枚数",
        "Back": "the number of flat things",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1318
    },
    {
        "Front": "毎度",
        "Back": "each time,common service-sector greeting",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1319
    },
    {
        "Front": "マイナス",
        "Back": "minus",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "巻く",
        "Back": "to wind,to coil,to roll",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1320
    },
    {
        "Front": "蒔く",
        "Back": "to sow (seeds)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1321
    },
    {
        "Front": "撒く",
        "Back": "to scatter,to sprinkle,to sow",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1322
    },
    {
        "Front": "枕",
        "Back": "pillow,bolster",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1323
    },
    {
        "Front": "曲げる",
        "Back": "to bend,to crook,to lean",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1324
    },
    {
        "Front": "まごまご",
        "Back": "confused",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "摩擦",
        "Back": "friction,rubbing,rubdown,chafe",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1325
    },
    {
        "Front": "混ざる",
        "Back": "to be mixed,to be blended with,to associate with,to mingle with,to join",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1326
    },
    {
        "Front": "交ざる",
        "Back": "to be mixed,to be blended with,to associate with,to mingle with,to join",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1327
    },
    {
        "Front": "混じる",
        "Back": "to be mixed,to be blended with,to associate with",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1328
    },
    {
        "Front": "交じる",
        "Back": "to be mixed,to be blended with,to associate with",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1329
    },
    {
        "Front": "マスク",
        "Back": "mask",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "混ぜる",
        "Back": "to mix,to stir",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1330
    },
    {
        "Front": "交ぜる",
        "Back": "to be mixed,to be blended with",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1331
    },
    {
        "Front": "またぐ",
        "Back": "to straddle",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "又は",
        "Back": "or,otherwise",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1332
    },
    {
        "Front": "待合室",
        "Back": "waiting room",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1333
    },
    {
        "Front": "待ち合わせる",
        "Back": "to rendezvous,to meet at a prearranged place and time",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1334
    },
    {
        "Front": "街角",
        "Back": "street corner",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1335
    },
    {
        "Front": "真っ暗",
        "Back": "total darkness,shortsightedness,pitch dark",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1336
    },
    {
        "Front": "真っ黒",
        "Back": "pitch black",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1337
    },
    {
        "Front": "真っ青",
        "Back": "deep blue,ghastly pale",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1338
    },
    {
        "Front": "真っ先",
        "Back": "the head,the foremost,beginning",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1339
    },
    {
        "Front": "真っ白",
        "Back": "pure white",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1340
    },
    {
        "Front": "祭る",
        "Back": "to deify,to enshrine",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1341
    },
    {
        "Front": "窓口",
        "Back": "ticket window",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1342
    },
    {
        "Front": "纏まる",
        "Back": "to be collected,to be settled,to be in order",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1343
    },
    {
        "Front": "纏める",
        "Back": "to put in order,to collect,to bring to a conclusion",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1344
    },
    {
        "Front": "真似る",
        "Back": "to mimic,to imitate",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1345
    },
    {
        "Front": "まぶしい",
        "Back": "dazzling,radiant",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "まぶた",
        "Back": "eyelids",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "マフラー",
        "Back": "muffler,scarf",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "間も無く",
        "Back": "soon,before long,in a short time",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1346
    },
    {
        "Front": "マラソン",
        "Back": "marathon",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "円い",
        "Back": "round,circular,spherical",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1347
    },
    {
        "Front": "稀",
        "Back": "rare,seldom",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1348
    },
    {
        "Front": "回り道",
        "Back": "detour",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1349
    },
    {
        "Front": "満員",
        "Back": "full house,no vacancy,sold out",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1350
    },
    {
        "Front": "マンション",
        "Back": "large apartment,apartment house",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "満点",
        "Back": "perfect score",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1351
    },
    {
        "Front": "見送る",
        "Back": "(1) to see off,to farewell,(2) to escort,(3) to let pass",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1352
    },
    {
        "Front": "見下ろす",
        "Back": "to overlook,to command a view of,to look down on something",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1353
    },
    {
        "Front": "見掛け",
        "Back": "outward appearance",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1354
    },
    {
        "Front": "三日月",
        "Back": "new moon,crescent moon",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1355
    },
    {
        "Front": "岬",
        "Back": "cape (on coast)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1356
    },
    {
        "Front": "みじめ",
        "Back": "(arch) sad,pitiful,wretched",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ミシン",
        "Back": "sewing machine",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "店屋",
        "Back": "store,shop",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1357
    },
    {
        "Front": "見出し",
        "Back": "heading,caption,subtitle,index",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1358
    },
    {
        "Front": "道順",
        "Back": "itinerary,route",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1359
    },
    {
        "Front": "見付かる",
        "Back": "to be found,to be discovered",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1360
    },
    {
        "Front": "見付ける",
        "Back": "to be familiar,to discover,to detect",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1361
    },
    {
        "Front": "みっともない",
        "Back": "shameful,indecent",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "見直す",
        "Back": "to look again,to get a better opinion of",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1362
    },
    {
        "Front": "見慣れる",
        "Back": "to become used to seeing,to be familiar with",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1363
    },
    {
        "Front": "醜い",
        "Back": "ugly",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1364
    },
    {
        "Front": "実る",
        "Back": "to bear fruit,to ripen",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1365
    },
    {
        "Front": "身分",
        "Back": "social position,social status",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1366
    },
    {
        "Front": "見本",
        "Back": "sample",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1367
    },
    {
        "Front": "見舞う",
        "Back": "to ask after (health),to visit",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1368
    },
    {
        "Front": "未満",
        "Back": "less than,insufficient",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1369
    },
    {
        "Front": "名字",
        "Back": "surname,family name",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1370
    },
    {
        "Front": "ミリ",
        "Back": "milli-,10^-3",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "診る",
        "Back": "to examine (medical)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1372
    },
    {
        "Front": "民間",
        "Back": "private,civilian,civil,popular,folk,unofficial",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1373
    },
    {
        "Front": "民謡",
        "Back": "folk song,popular song",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1374
    },
    {
        "Front": "向う",
        "Back": "(v5u) to face,to go towards",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1375
    },
    {
        "Front": "剥く",
        "Back": "to peel,to skin,to pare,to hull",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1376
    },
    {
        "Front": "無限",
        "Back": "infinite",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1377
    },
    {
        "Front": "無地",
        "Back": "plain,unfigured",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1378
    },
    {
        "Front": "蒸し暑い",
        "Back": "humid,sultry",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1379
    },
    {
        "Front": "矛盾",
        "Back": "contradiction,inconsistency",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1380
    },
    {
        "Front": "蒸す",
        "Back": "to steam,to poultice,to be sultry",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1381
    },
    {
        "Front": "無数",
        "Back": "countless number,infinite number",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1382
    },
    {
        "Front": "紫",
        "Back": "purple colour,violet",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1383
    },
    {
        "Front": "群れ",
        "Back": "group,crowd,flock,herd",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1384
    },
    {
        "Front": "姪",
        "Back": "niece",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1385
    },
    {
        "Front": "名作",
        "Back": "masterpiece",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1386
    },
    {
        "Front": "名刺",
        "Back": "business card",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1387
    },
    {
        "Front": "名詞",
        "Back": "noun",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1388
    },
    {
        "Front": "名所",
        "Back": "famous place",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1389
    },
    {
        "Front": "命ずる",
        "Back": "to command,to appoint",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1390
    },
    {
        "Front": "迷信",
        "Back": "superstition",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1391
    },
    {
        "Front": "名物",
        "Back": "famous product,special product,speciality",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1392
    },
    {
        "Front": "銘々",
        "Back": "each,individual",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1393
    },
    {
        "Front": "目上",
        "Back": "superior(s),senior",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1394
    },
    {
        "Front": "メーター",
        "Back": "meter (clock)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "恵まれる",
        "Back": "to be blessed with,to be rich in",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1395
    },
    {
        "Front": "巡る",
        "Back": "to go around",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1396
    },
    {
        "Front": "目指す",
        "Back": "to aim at,to have an eye on",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1397
    },
    {
        "Front": "目覚し",
        "Back": "(abbr) alarm-clock",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1398
    },
    {
        "Front": "目下",
        "Back": "at present,now",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1399
    },
    {
        "Front": "目印",
        "Back": "mark,sign,landmark",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1400
    },
    {
        "Front": "目立つ",
        "Back": "to be conspicuous,to stand out",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1401
    },
    {
        "Front": "めちゃくちゃ",
        "Back": "absurd,unreasonable,excessive,messed up,spoiled,wreaked",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "めっきり",
        "Back": "remarkably",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "めでたい",
        "Back": "happy,simple soul,propitious,joyous",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "メニュー",
        "Back": "menu",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "めまい",
        "Back": "dizziness,giddiness",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "目安",
        "Back": "criterion,aim",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1402
    },
    {
        "Front": "免税",
        "Back": "tax exemption,duty exemption",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1403
    },
    {
        "Front": "面積",
        "Back": "area",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1404
    },
    {
        "Front": "面接",
        "Back": "interview",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1405
    },
    {
        "Front": "面倒臭い",
        "Back": "bother to do,tiresome",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1406
    },
    {
        "Front": "儲かる",
        "Back": "to be profitable,to yield a profit",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1407
    },
    {
        "Front": "儲ける",
        "Back": "to get,to earn,to gain,to have (bear, beget) a child",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1408
    },
    {
        "Front": "申し訳ない",
        "Back": "inexcusable",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1409
    },
    {
        "Front": "モーター",
        "Back": "motor",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "木材",
        "Back": "lumber,timber,wood",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1410
    },
    {
        "Front": "目次",
        "Back": "table of contents",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1411
    },
    {
        "Front": "潜る",
        "Back": "(1) to drive,to pass through,(2) to evade,to hide,(3) to dive (into or under water),to go undergroun",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1412
    },
    {
        "Front": "もしかしたら",
        "Back": "perhaps,maybe,by some chance",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "もしかすると",
        "Back": "perhaps,maybe,by some chance",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "もたれる",
        "Back": "to lean against,to lean on,to recline on,to lie heavy (on the stomach)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "モダン",
        "Back": "modern",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "餅",
        "Back": "sticky rice cake",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1413
    },
    {
        "Front": "もったいない",
        "Back": "too good,more than one deserves,wasteful,sacrilegious,unworthy of",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "モデル",
        "Back": "model",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "元々",
        "Back": "originally,by nature,from the start",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1414
    },
    {
        "Front": "物置",
        "Back": "storage room",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1415
    },
    {
        "Front": "物語る",
        "Back": "to tell,to indicate",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1416
    },
    {
        "Front": "物差し",
        "Back": "ruler,measure",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1417
    },
    {
        "Front": "物凄い",
        "Back": "earth-shattering,staggering,to a very great extent",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1418
    },
    {
        "Front": "モノレール",
        "Back": "monorail",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "揉む",
        "Back": "to rub,to crumple (up),to wrinkle",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1419
    },
    {
        "Front": "燃やす",
        "Back": "to burn",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1420
    },
    {
        "Front": "催し",
        "Back": "event,festivities,function",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1421
    },
    {
        "Front": "盛る",
        "Back": "(1) to serve (food, etc.),(2) to fill up,(3) to prescribe",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1422
    },
    {
        "Front": "問答",
        "Back": "questions and answers,dialogue",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1423
    },
    {
        "Front": "やかましい",
        "Back": "(1) noisy,(2) strict,fussy",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "夜間",
        "Back": "at night,nighttime",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1424
    },
    {
        "Front": "薬缶",
        "Back": "kettle",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1425
    },
    {
        "Front": "役者",
        "Back": "actor,actress",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1426
    },
    {
        "Front": "役所",
        "Back": "government office,public office",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1427
    },
    {
        "Front": "訳す",
        "Back": "to translate",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1428
    },
    {
        "Front": "役人",
        "Back": "government official",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1429
    },
    {
        "Front": "薬品",
        "Back": "medicine(s),chemical(s)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1430
    },
    {
        "Front": "役目",
        "Back": "duty,business",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1431
    },
    {
        "Front": "火傷",
        "Back": "burn,scald",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1432
    },
    {
        "Front": "夜行",
        "Back": "walking around at night,night train,night travel",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1433
    },
    {
        "Front": "矢印",
        "Back": "directing arrow",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1434
    },
    {
        "Front": "やたらに",
        "Back": "randomly,recklessly,blindly",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "薬局",
        "Back": "pharmacy,drugstore",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1435
    },
    {
        "Front": "やっつける",
        "Back": "to attack (an enemy),to beat,to do away with,to finish off",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "家主",
        "Back": "landlord",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1436
    },
    {
        "Front": "やっぱり",
        "Back": "also,as I thought,still,in spite of,absolutely,of course",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "破く",
        "Back": "",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1437
    },
    {
        "Front": "破れる",
        "Back": "to get torn,to wear out",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1438
    },
    {
        "Front": "やむをえない",
        "Back": "cannot be helped,unavoidable",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "軟らかい",
        "Back": "soft,tender,limp",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1439
    },
    {
        "Front": "遊園地",
        "Back": "amusement park",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1440
    },
    {
        "Front": "夕刊",
        "Back": "evening paper",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1441
    },
    {
        "Front": "友好",
        "Back": "friendship",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1442
    },
    {
        "Front": "郵送",
        "Back": "mailing",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1443
    },
    {
        "Front": "夕立",
        "Back": "(sudden) evening shower (rain)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1444
    },
    {
        "Front": "夕日",
        "Back": "(in) the evening sun,setting sun",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1445
    },
    {
        "Front": "悠々",
        "Back": "quiet,calm,leisurely",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1446
    },
    {
        "Front": "有料",
        "Back": "admission-paid,toll",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1447
    },
    {
        "Front": "浴衣",
        "Back": "bathrobe,informal summer kimono,yukata",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1448
    },
    {
        "Front": "湯気",
        "Back": "steam,vapour",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1449
    },
    {
        "Front": "輸血",
        "Back": "blood transfusion",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1450
    },
    {
        "Front": "輸送",
        "Back": "transport,transportation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1451
    },
    {
        "Front": "油断",
        "Back": "negligence,unpreparedness",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1452
    },
    {
        "Front": "ゆでる",
        "Back": "to boil",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "湯飲み",
        "Back": "teacup",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1453
    },
    {
        "Front": "緩い",
        "Back": "loose,lenient,slow",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1454
    },
    {
        "Front": "溶岩",
        "Back": "lava",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1455
    },
    {
        "Front": "容器",
        "Back": "container,vessel",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1456
    },
    {
        "Front": "用語",
        "Back": "term,terminology",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1457
    },
    {
        "Front": "要旨",
        "Back": "gist,essentials,summary,fundamentals",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1458
    },
    {
        "Front": "幼児",
        "Back": "infant,baby,child",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1459
    },
    {
        "Front": "容積",
        "Back": "capacity,volume",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1460
    },
    {
        "Front": "幼稚",
        "Back": "infancy,childish,infantile",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1461
    },
    {
        "Front": "幼稚園",
        "Back": "kindergarten",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1462
    },
    {
        "Front": "用途",
        "Back": "use,usefulness",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1463
    },
    {
        "Front": "洋品店",
        "Back": "shop which handles Western-style apparel and accessories",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1464
    },
    {
        "Front": "養分",
        "Back": "nourishment,nutrient",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1465
    },
    {
        "Front": "羊毛",
        "Back": "wool",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1466
    },
    {
        "Front": "漸く",
        "Back": "gradually,finally,hardly",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1467
    },
    {
        "Front": "要領",
        "Back": "point,gist,essentials,outline",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1468
    },
    {
        "Front": "欲張り",
        "Back": "avarice,covetousness,greed",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1469
    },
    {
        "Front": "余計",
        "Back": "too much,unnecessary,abundance,surplus,excess,superfluity",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1470
    },
    {
        "Front": "よこす",
        "Back": "(1) to send,to forward,(2) to hand over (e.g. money)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "汚す",
        "Back": "(1) to disgrace,to dishonour,(2) to pollute,to contaminate,to soil,to make dirty,to stain",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1471
    },
    {
        "Front": "寄せる",
        "Back": "to collect,to gather,to add,to put aside",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1472
    },
    {
        "Front": "余所",
        "Back": "another place,somewhere else,strange parts",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1473
    },
    {
        "Front": "四つ角",
        "Back": "four corners,crossroads",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1474
    },
    {
        "Front": "酔っ払い",
        "Back": "drunkard",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1475
    },
    {
        "Front": "予備",
        "Back": "preparation,preliminaries,reserve,spare",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1476
    },
    {
        "Front": "呼び掛ける",
        "Back": "to call out to,to accost,to address (crowd),to appeal",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1477
    },
    {
        "Front": "呼び出す",
        "Back": "to summon,to call (e.g. phone)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1478
    },
    {
        "Front": "蘇る",
        "Back": "to be resurrected,to be revived,to be resuscitated,to be rehabilitated",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1479
    },
    {
        "Front": "因る",
        "Back": "to come from",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1480
    },
    {
        "Front": "慶び",
        "Back": "(n) (a) joy,(a) delight,rapture,pleasure,gratification,rejoicing,congratulations,felicitations",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1481
    },
    {
        "Front": "慶ぶ",
        "Back": "",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1482
    },
    {
        "Front": "来日",
        "Back": "arrival in Japan,coming to Japan,visit to Japan",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1483
    },
    {
        "Front": "落第",
        "Back": "failure,dropping out of a class",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1484
    },
    {
        "Front": "ラッシュアワー",
        "Back": "rush hour",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "欄",
        "Back": "column of text (e.g. as in a newspaper)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1485
    },
    {
        "Front": "ランチ",
        "Back": "launch,lunch",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ランニング",
        "Back": "(1) running,(2) tank top",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "乱暴",
        "Back": "rude,violent,rough,lawless,unreasonable,reckless",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1486
    },
    {
        "Front": "理科",
        "Back": "science",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1487
    },
    {
        "Front": "利害",
        "Back": "advantages and disadvantages,interest",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1488
    },
    {
        "Front": "リズム",
        "Back": "rhythm",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "リットル",
        "Back": "litre",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "リボン",
        "Back": "ribbon",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "略す",
        "Back": "to abbreviate",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1489
    },
    {
        "Front": "流域",
        "Back": "(river) basin",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1490
    },
    {
        "Front": "寮",
        "Back": "hostel,dormitory",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1491
    },
    {
        "Front": "両側",
        "Back": "both sides",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1492
    },
    {
        "Front": "漁師",
        "Back": "fisherman",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1493
    },
    {
        "Front": "領事",
        "Back": "consul",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1494
    },
    {
        "Front": "領収",
        "Back": "receipt,voucher",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1495
    },
    {
        "Front": "臨時",
        "Back": "temporary,special,extraordinary",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1496
    },
    {
        "Front": "留守番",
        "Back": "care-taking,caretaker,house-watching",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1497
    },
    {
        "Front": "例外",
        "Back": "exception",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1498
    },
    {
        "Front": "零点",
        "Back": "zero,no marks",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1499
    },
    {
        "Front": "冷凍",
        "Back": "freezing,cold storage,refrigeration",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1500
    },
    {
        "Front": "レインコート",
        "Back": "raincoat",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "レクリェーション",
        "Back": "recreation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "レジャー",
        "Back": "leisure",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "列島",
        "Back": "chain of islands",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1501
    },
    {
        "Front": "レベル",
        "Back": "level",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "リポート",
        "Back": "report,paper",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "煉瓦",
        "Back": "brick",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1502
    },
    {
        "Front": "連合",
        "Back": "union,alliance",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1503
    },
    {
        "Front": "レンズ",
        "Back": "lens",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "蝋燭",
        "Back": "candle",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1504
    },
    {
        "Front": "ローマじ",
        "Back": "romanization,Roman letters",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "録音",
        "Back": "(audio) recording",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1505
    },
    {
        "Front": "ロッカー",
        "Back": "locker",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ロビー",
        "Back": "lobby",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "論ずる",
        "Back": "to argue,to discuss,to debate",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1506
    },
    {
        "Front": "和英",
        "Back": "Japanese-English",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1507
    },
    {
        "Front": "分る",
        "Back": "to be understood",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1508
    },
    {
        "Front": "分かれる",
        "Back": "to branch off,to diverge from,to fork,to split,to dispense,to scatter,to divide into",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1509
    },
    {
        "Front": "若々しい",
        "Back": "youthful,young",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1510
    },
    {
        "Front": "湧く",
        "Back": "to boil,to grow hot,to get excited,to gush forth",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1511
    },
    {
        "Front": "詫びる",
        "Back": "to apologize",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1512
    },
    {
        "Front": "和服",
        "Back": "Japanese clothes",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1513
    },
    {
        "Front": "わりあいに",
        "Back": "comparatively",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "割算",
        "Back": "division (math)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1514
    },
    {
        "Front": "割と",
        "Back": "relatively, comparitively",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1515
    },
    {
        "Front": "割引",
        "Back": "discount,reduction,rebate",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1516
    },
    {
        "Front": "椀",
        "Back": "Japanese soup bowl,wooden bowl",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1517
    },
    {
        "Front": "碗",
        "Back": "bowl",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1518
    },
    {
        "Front": "ワンピース",
        "Back": "one-piece dress",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n2-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    }
]